<resources>
    <string name="app_name">R6 Companion</string>

    <string name="key_preferences">com.zeuspalette.android.r6tab.saved_data</string>

    <string name="nav_drawer_attackers">Attackers</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_defenders">Defenders</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_units">Units</string>
    <string name="nav_drawer_weapons">Weapons</string>
    <string name="nav_main_info">Information</string>

    <string name="nav_bottom_info">Info</string>
    <string name="nav_bottom_primary">Primary</string>
    <string name="nav_bottom_secondary">Secondary</string>
    <string name="nav_bottom_gadget">Gadget</string>

    <string name="background">Background</string>
    <string name="profile">Psychological Profile</string>
    <string name="training">Training</string>
    <string name="experience">Experience</string>
    <string name="notes">Notes</string>

    <string name="title_firerate">Fire Rate</string>
    <string name="title_mobility">Mobility</string>
    <string name="title_capacity">Capacity</string>
    <string name="title_scope">Scopes</string>
    <string name="title_barrel">Barrels</string>
    <string name="title_underbarrel">Underbarrels</string>
    <string name="title_grip">Grips</string>
    <string name="title_comment">Notes</string>
    <string name="title_damage">Damage</string>
    <string name="title_stats">Stats</string>
    <string name="title_help_notes">Enter notes here ..</string>


    <string name="no_grip">No Grips Available</string>
    <string name="no_barrel">No Barrels Available</string>
    <string name="no_underbarrel">No Underbarrels Available</string>
    <string name="no_scope">No Scopes Available</string>
    <string name="no_sight">No Sights Available</string>

    <string name="flashbang">Flashbang</string>
    <string name="grenade">Grenade</string>
    <string name="breach">Breaching Charge</string>
    <string name="wire">Barbed Wire</string>
    <string name="shield">Shield</string>


    <!-- INFORMATION -->
    <string name="dialog_r">Thanks for installing R6 Companion. This app will always be free.Take a moment to share and rate us so that we can reach to more people.</string>
    <string name="dialog_1">This section shows you all the Attackers. Click on any Attacker to explore the details about their Weapons, Gadgets and  Abilities</string>
    <string name="dialog_2">This section shows you all the Defenders. Click on any Defender to explore the details about their Weapons, Gadgets and  Abilities</string>
    <string name="dialog_3">This section shows you all the available Units. Click on any Unit to learn about them and check the list of Operators under them</string>
    <string name="dialog_4">This section shows you all the Weapon Categories. Click on any Category to checkout all Weapons in that category.You can also click on [SHOW ALL] button to take a peek into the list of Weapons in that category</string>
    <string name="dialog_5">This section shows basic information about the Operator</string>
    <string name="dialog_6">This section shows the Primary Weapon loadout of the Operator. You can also take notes for individual Weapons on what attachments you prefer</string>
    <string name="dialog_7">This section shows the Secondary Weapon loadout of the Operator. You can also take notes for individual Weapons on what attachments you prefer</string>
    <string name="dialog_8">This section shows the Primary and Secondary Gadgets of the Operator. You can also find tips on how to use the Operator</string>
    <string name="dialog_9">This section shows the Attackers sorted by Speed and Armor</string>
    <string name="dialog_10">This section shows the Defenders sorted by Speed and Armor</string>


    <string name="dialog_n"></string>

    <!-- SLEDGE -->

    <string name="sledge_name">Seamus Cowden</string>
    <string name="sledge_dob">April 2nd, 1982</string>
    <string name="sledge_weight">1.92 M</string>
    <string name="sledge_height">95 KG</string>
    <string name="sledge_background">Seamus Cowden hails from the upper tip of Scottish Highlands. Due to his imposing physical presence and athleticism, he found early success as the Captain of the 1998 Scotland National under-20 Rugby Union Team. A strong desire for public service inspired Cowden to enlist in the army at 18, after five years on active duty, he was recruited by the S.A.S.</string>
    <string name="sledge_profile">Cowden displays natural leadership qualities, likely developed during his amateur sports career. This comfort on the front line can be attributed to his confidence and tactical experience.</string>
    <string name="sledge_training">British Army: 3rd (UK) Division \n\nS.A.S Operative</string>
    <string name="sledge_experience">Holds the all-time speed and strength record for the S.A.S qualifying physical exam. Seamus Cowden developed an operational expertise in breaking down barriers with a breaching hammer.</string>
    <string name="sledge_notes">Seamus Cowden was integral to the S.A.S, and his recruitment to Rainbow squad is a major coup for their operations. His professionalism and tactical abilities are beyond reproach, and he is expected to perform at the highest level in his new role.</string>
    <string name="sledge_gadget_name">THE CABER</string>
    <string name="sledge_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Breaching Hammer</string>
    <string name="sledge_gadget">Sledge use a Breaching Hammer to breach through walls.</string>
    <string name="sledge_gadget_one">Forged machined head for hammering and ramming with maximum damage and minimum slip.Forged machined head for hammering and ramming with maximum damage and minimum slip.</string>
    <string name="sledge_gadget_two">Molded fiberglass handle with two molded rings equally spaced to create stoppers preventing the operator\'s hands from slipping when ramming or swinging at objects.</string>
    <string name="sledge_gadget_three">Forged crowbar end.</string>

    <!-- THATCHER -->
    <string name="thatcher_name">Mike Baker</string>
    <string name="thatcher_dob">June 22nd,1961</string>
    <string name="thatcher_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="thatcher_height">72 KG</string>
    <string name="thatcher_background">Born into a family of stevedores, Baker enlisted for active military duty on his eighteenth birthday. A veteran of three wars, Baker was the oldest S.A.S operative on active duty until he was recruited by Rainbow.</string>
    <string name="thatcher_profile">Baker is highly observant, calculating and decisive. While his demeanor may denote traces of impatient cynicism, Baker possesses a profound sense of ethical responsibility. It is recommended to assign Baker with junior operators of strong moral conviction, whom he can mentor.</string>
    <string name="thatcher_training">British Army : Parachute Regiment \n\nBritish Army : S.A.S Bravo Two Zero \n\nBritish Army : S.A.S Warrant Officer Class 1 </string>
    <string name="thatcher_experience">Baker\'s exemplary performance, on and off the battlefield, during two politically charged conflicts made him a natural fit for VIP protection duty. He is highly proficient in close quarters combat, and is a world caliber expert in anti-electronics operation.</string>
    <string name="thatcher_notes">Saw action at the battle of Goose Green during the Falklands Conflict. On Team Blue of Operation Nimrod (Iranian Embassy siege, 1980). Veteran of unit Bravo Two Zero during Gulf War (1991).</string>
    <string name="thatcher_gadget_name">EMP GRENADE</string>
    <string name="thatcher_gadget_name_byline">EG MKO-EMP Grenade</string>
    <string name="thatcher_gadget">Thatcher uses EMP grenade to disable any electronics in range.</string>
    <string name="thatcher_gadget_one">The copper spool builds the EMP by spinning.</string>
    <string name="thatcher_gadget_two">Twist top 45 degrees to activate the device.</string>

    <!-- ASH -->
    <string name="ash_name">Eliza Cohen</string>
    <string name="ash_dob">December 24th, 1983</string>
    <string name="ash_weight">1.70 M</string>
    <string name="ash_height">63 KG</string>
    <string name="ash_background">Cohen was born and raised in Jerusalem. After secondary school,she enrolled at Tel Aviv University, in the Engineering program, where she did a semester abroad at Boston University. After college she performed her civic duty enlisting in the Israeli Defense Forces. Her background in engineering made her a prime candidate for mechanical maintenance and demolitions.</string>
    <string name="ash_profile">Her military training as a demolitions specialist has left Cohen with an inflated sense of self. She can be aggressive, impulsive and overly confident. She is quick to action, which can be an asset or fatal for someone in her line of work.</string>
    <string name="ash_training">Tel Aviv University: Bachelor of Science, Engineering. \n\nIsraeli Air Forces \n\nShaldag \n\nFBI SWAT (JINSA LEEP)</string>
    <string name="ash_experience">Second Lebanon War \n\nOperation Orchard \n\nAustere Challenge</string>
    <string name="ash_notes">None</string>
    <string name="ash_gadget_name">M120 CREM</string>
    <string name="ash_gadget_name_byline">Compact Rifle Entry Munition</string>
    <string name="ash_gadget">Ash fires an explosive Breach Round that burrows into a surface and automatically detonates.</string>
    <string name="ash_gadget_one">Modified grenade launcher.</string>
    <string name="ash_gadget_two">40mm breaching round.</string>

    <!-- THERMITE -->

    <string name="thermite_name">Jordan Trace</string>
    <string name="thermite_dob">March 14th, 1982</string>
    <string name="thermite_weight">1.78 M</string>
    <string name="thermite_height">80 KG</string>
    <string name="thermite_background">Trace joined the marines after high school, serving two tours in Iraq. After his discharge he used his GI Bill money to put himself through college at Texas A\-M and earned a Bachelor of Science in Chemistry. He then joined the FBI. After four years as a field agent he transferred to FBI SWAT.</string>
    <string name="thermite_profile">Regimented, disciplined, orderly, these are some of the words people use to describe Trace. He knows when to relax, especially in social situations. He takes pride in knowing all of the variables. Trace prefers to be the one in control rather than leave things in chance.</string>
    <string name="thermite_training">USMC Close Quarters Battle School \n\nUSMC Methods of Entry \n\nUSMC Helicopter and Rope Suspension Techniques Course \n\nTexas A\-M: Bachelor of Science, Chemistry \n\nFBI Field Agent \n\nFBI Swat</string>
    <string name="thermite_experience">Two tours of duty in Iraq \n\nFleet Antiterrorism Security Teams (FAST)</string>
    <string name="thermite_notes">None</string>
    <string name="thermite_gadget_name">BRIMSTONE BC-3</string>
    <string name="thermite_gadget_name_byline">Exothermic Charge</string>
    <string name="thermite_gadget">Thermite sets an exothermic charge that destroys reinforced walls.</string>
    <string name="thermite_gadget_one">Remote detonated.</string>
    <string name="thermite_gadget_two">Rolling mat affixed to an incendiary device.</string>


    <!-- TWITCH -->

    <string name="twitch_name">Emmanuelle Pichon</string>
    <string name="twitch_dob">October 12th, 1988</string>
    <string name="twitch_weight">1.68 M</string>
    <string name="twitch_height">58 KG</string>
    <string name="twitch_background">Born in the historic town of Nancy, Pichon grew up in a family that valued education, particularly math and science. Early participation in sponsored computer programming competitions led to her joining the army cadets at sixteen.</string>
    <string name="twitch_profile">Pichon demonstrates an affinity for complex robotic systems and mechanical academia, due to an early exposure to analytical problem-solving. This ability transcends academia. Unlike many engineers who have the propensity to be emotionally disconnected or apathetic, Pichon is strongly intuitive and empathetic. She believes that technology\'s best use is to improve the quality of life. This principle motivates Pichon in her military service.
</string>
    <string name="twitch_training">Chad \n\nLibya</string>
    <string name="twitch_experience">GIGN</string>
    <string name="twitch_notes">Despite her young age, Pichon shows exemplary promise as a support specialist. At twenty years old, she was the youngest operative to ever be accepted into the GIGN.</string>
    <string name="twitch_gadget_name">RSD MODEL 1</string>
    <string name="twitch_gadget_name_byline">Shock Drone</string>
    <string name="twitch_gadget">Used two shock drones to disable traps and injure enemies.</string>
    <string name="twitch_gadget_one">The chassis holds multiple shots.</string>
    <string name="twitch_gadget_two">Bulkier than a standard observation drone, the shock drone is also slower and can\'t jump</string>

    <!-- MONTAGNE -->
    <string name="montagne_name">Gilles Toure</string>
    <string name="montagne_dob">October 11th, 1968</string>
    <string name="montagne_weight">1.90 M</string>
    <string name="montagne_height">90 KG</string>
    <string name="montagne_background">The son of an army officer and school teacher, Montagne\'s family was stationed near Bordeaux, France. A few years after he graduated from high school, Montagne became a member of the National Gendarmerie. Dedicating his life to the defense work, his commitment has allowed him to obtain a position on the GIGN. </string>
    <string name="montagne_profile">Toure is considered highly dependable by his peers. His steady nerves have allowed him to successfully take control of complex, high stress situations during the tenure of his career. As a  trainer, Toure is stern with the new recruits but always tries to remain fair. He prefers to lead by example.</string>
    <string name="montagne_training">National Gendarmerie \n\nGIGN</string>
    <string name="montagne_experience">1994 French Airline hijacking \n\nWon several CQB awards in SWAT competitions \n\nCertified GIGN trainer</string>
    <string name="montagne_notes">None</string>
    <string name="montagne_gadget_name">LE ROC</string>
    <string name="montagne_gadget_name_byline">Extendable Shield</string>
    <string name="montagne_gadget">Can expand his Extendable Shield to offer full protection while standing</string>
    <string name="montagne_gadget_one">Collapses into half its size, providing increased mobility to its wielder</string>
    <string name="montagne_gadget_two">Composite of reinforced alloys and Kevlar</string>
    <string name="montagne_gadget_three">Provides protection against small-arms fire and close combat attacks</string>


    <!-- GLAZ -->

    <string name="glaz_name">Timur Glazkov</string>
    <string name="glaz_dob">July 2nd,1987</string>
    <string name="glaz_weight">1.787 M</string>
    <string name="glaz_height">79 KG</string>
    <string name="glaz_background">Born and raised in Vladivostok, where his father worked in the shipping industry. Glaskov studied art in secondary school, until the Beslan school hostage crisis inspired him top transfer to the Cader Corps and pursue a career in the armed forces.</string>
    <string name="glaz_profile">While Timur doesn\'t thrive in large groups, he is engaging and expressive in one-on-one conversations. He has a patient temperament and can be very introspective. His background as an artist, his curiosity, and attention to detail has trained him to be mindful and precise. This trait makes Timur an excellent sniper and spotter.</string>
    <string name="glaz_training">Cadet Corps \n\nGround Forces of Russian Federation \n\nKhabarovsk Military Commanders Training Academy \n\nSpetnaz: 45th Guards Regiment</string>
    <string name="glaz_experience">Saw action in the 2008 South Ossetia War. \n\nDeployed in REDACTED</string>
    <string name="glaz_notes">While he is quiet in person he is a skilled painter. His art is expressive and colorful, a start contrast to his military life.</string>
    <string name="glaz_gadget_name">HDS FLIP SIGHT</string>
    <string name="glaz_gadget_name_byline">Thermal sights through Smoke</string>
    <string name="glaz_gadget">Glaz toggles a magnification scope with sophisticated image sensors outlining long range marks, even through smoke.</string>
    <string name="glaz_gadget_one">The scope is mounted on a hinge to flip into position</string>


    <!-- FUZE -->

    <string name="fuze_name">Shuhrat Kessikbayev</string>
    <string name="fuze_dob">October 12th,1982</string>
    <string name="fuze_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="fuze_height">80 KG</string>
    <string name="fuze_background">Kessikbayev grew up in a military family in Samarkand, Uzbekistan. After his family emigrated to Russia shortly before the collapse of the Soviet Union, Kessikbayev followed in his father\'s footsteps and enrolled in the military, where his facility with technology earned him a spot in coveted weapon testing brigade at Albino firing range near Moscow.</string>
    <string name="fuze_profile">Kessikbayev is an expert tinkerer and master craft-man, more at ease with the workings of machines than people. His gruff demeanor and curt speech should not be mistake for misanthropy. He possessed a strong moral conviction.</string>
    <string name="fuze_training">27th Motor Rifle Brigade \n\nSpetznaz GRU GSO</string>
    <string name="fuze_experience">Participant in the Ratnik experimental weaponry brigade. \n\nPersonal cluster charge, the \"Matryoshka\" , designed by Kessikbayev first saw action in REDACTED</string>
    <string name="fuze_notes">While not a likely candidate for a squad leadership position. Shuhrat Kessikbayev\'s unique abilities and technical know-how make him a extremely useful asset to Rainbow.</string>
    <string name="fuze_gadget_name">APM-6 \"MATRYOSHKA\"</string>
    <string name="fuze_gadget_name_byline">Cluster Charge</string>
    <string name="fuze_gadget">Fuze uses Cluster Charges that pierce and stick to walls, releasing sub-grenades on the opposing side.</string>
    <string name="fuze_gadget_one">Once anchored, the piston burrows through walls or floors</string>
    <string name="fuze_gadget_two">Live cluster grenades</string>


    <!-- BLITZ -->

    <string name="blitz_name">Elias Kotz</string>
    <string name="blitz_dob">April 2nd, 1980</string>
    <string name="blitz_weight">1.75 M</string>
    <string name="blitz_height">75 KG</string>
    <string name="blitz_background">A student of Hermann-Bose-Gymnasium, Kotz excelled academically and as a sport-man in HBG\'s bilingual program. His imposing physique made him an exceptional athlete, he carried his excellence on the field into his military training. \n\nHis jovial nature and academic background eased the transition from a Schnelle Krafte soldier in Kosovo to a member of GSG 9. Kotz was integral to establishing an anti-terrorism unit in India following the 2008 attack in Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="blitz_profile">Kotz has seen his share of battlefield horrors but is mentally resilient. He uses humor to disarm and as a device to manage stress during operation. He is the first to rush a barricade and is  always willing to place the  team safety over his own. Kotz rejects the concept that his deeds are in some way heroic. When faced with overt praise, he will become self-effacing.</string>
    <string name="blitz_training">International Baccalaureate Hermann-Bose-Gymnasium \n\nDivision Schnelle Krafte \n\nGSG9</string>
    <string name="blitz_experience">Kosovo \n\nMumbai, India (Trainer)</string>
    <string name="blitz_notes">None</string>
    <string name="blitz_gadget_name">G52-TACTICAL SHIELD</string>
    <string name="blitz_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Light Shield</string>
    <string name="blitz_gadget">Triggers the flash attached to his ballistic shield to temporarily blind enemies.</string>
    <string name="blitz_gadget_one">Ballistic shield</string>
    <string name="blitz_gadget_two">Three rows of eight flash-bang grenades provide a high intensity light source</string>


    <!-- IQ -->

    <string name="iq_name">Monika Weiss</string>
    <string name="iq_dob">August 1st, 1979</string>
    <string name="iq_weight">1.75M</string>
    <string name="iq_height">70 KG</string>
    <string name="iq_background">Weiss developed a knack for electrical engineering early in life. At sixteen she completed her first internship with a local tech company. She would continue her education at MIT and CalTech in United States. \n\nAfter university, she traveled for a year before dedicating her life to a new challenge, the Bundespolizei (BPOL). Weiss  thrived in her new environment and after two years with the BPOL she was recruited by GSG9.</string>
    <string name="iq_profile">A brilliant overachiever and a fast learner, Weiss has been successful at nearly everything she tries. This facility, however, has conditioned her to refuse failure as an acceptable outcome. This can manifest as borderline obsessive behavior when tacking obstacles that are perceived to be difficult or exceptionally challenging.</string>
    <string name="iq_training">Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT): Bachelor of Science Electrical Engineering \n\nCalTech : PhD Electrical Engineering \n\nBundespolizei</string>
    <string name="iq_experience">Iraq: GSG 9 protection detail \n\nGSG 9 technical unit \n\nGSG 9 Airborne Group \n\nSWAT traning with both Bundespolizei and GSG 9</string>
    <string name="iq_notes">None</string>
    <string name="iq_gadget_name">RED MKIII \"SPECTRE\"</string>
    <string name="iq_gadget_name_byline">Electronics Detector</string>
    <string name="iq_gadget">Uses a Electronics Detector to locate any electronics in range through obstacles such as walls</string>
    <string name="iq_gadget_one">Wrist-mounted</string>
    <string name="iq_gadget_two">Mobile phone-sized sensor</string>

    <!-- BUCK -->

    <string name="buck_name">Sebastien Cote</string>
    <string name="buck_dob">August 20th, 1980</string>
    <string name="buck_weight">1.78 M</string>
    <string name="buck_height">84 KG</string>
    <string name="buck_background">A Montreal native, Cote always wanted to lead an unconventional life. He enrolled in the Canadian Armed Forces via the Regular Officer Training Plan, which allowed him to attend University and obtain a degree in Criminology. After graduation he became an MP in the Canadian Army. \n\nWhen his time in the Army was completed he joined the Royal Canadian Mounted Police and eventually became part of the Emergency Response Team. After excelling in his ERT role he was invited by the Canadian Military to re-up and become member of the JTF2.</string>
    <string name="buck_profile">Highly pragmatic, Cote will always take the shortest distance between two points.He is not one to mince words, or become hyperbolic. He enjoys simple mechanical devices to the more high arsenal employed by the other members of Team Rainbow.</string>
    <string name="buck_training">Universite du Quebec a Montreal: Bachelor of Arts, Criminology \n\nRoyal Canadian Army Military Police \n\nRCMP ERT \nJTF2</string>
    <string name="buck_experience">Special Operations Coxswain Course \n\nNucler, Biological and Chemical Defense Course \n\nHostage Rescue and Special Protection operations training \n\nATF Task Force (Targeting international drug smuggling in Canada)</string>
    <string name="buck_notes">None</string>
    <string name="buck_gadget_name">SK 4-12 (SKELETON KEY)</string>
    <string name="buck_gadget_name_byline">An Effective Breaching tool</string>
    <string name="buck_gadget">Toggles under-barrel shotgun attachment on his main weapon.</string>
    <string name="buck_gadget_one">Under-barrel mounted 12 gauge shotgun with four round capacity, used in tandem with an assault rifle.</string>
    <string name="buck_gadget_two">The Skeleton Key allows the operator to alternate between their standard issue assault rifle and a breaching shotgun with ease and efficiency.</string>

    <!-- BLACKBEARD -->

    <string name="blackbeard_name">Craig Jenson</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_dob">March 12th, 1985</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_height">84 KG</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_background">Jenson grew up in a comfortable upper middle class family with no military history. He decided that he wanted to be a Navy SEAL at a young age and devoted his life to achieving the goal. With the help of his father, a kinesiology professor at University of Washington, he started training at twelve and enlisted in the Navy at eighteen.</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_profile">The drive and discipling seen in SEAL team members is what drew Jenson to be the group. He sees SEALs as an ideal blend of mental and physical abilities and strives to optimize both of these traits in himself.</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_training">Navy Diver \n\nBasic Underwater Demolition/SEAL training, Airborned jump school, Search and Rescue swimmer, CQB courses at Quantico \n\nNAVY SEAL</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_experience">Support role in counter piracy operations inclusing the Maersk Alabama Hijacking in 2009. \n\nDeployed in Afghanistan \n\nTook part in the raid of MV Morning Glory in Libya</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_notes">None</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_gadget_name">TARS MK 0</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_gadget_name_byline">Transparent Armoured Rifle Shield</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_gadget">Deploys a ballistic shield on his rifle that can be swapped if the first one gets damaged</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_gadget_one">Multiple layers of transparent polycarbonate and thermoplastic armor, coated with a spall shield and backed with ultra-light weight laminated glass.</string>
    <string name="blackbeard_gadget_two">Protects the user against blunt impact and artillery fire.</string>

    <!-- CAPITAO -->
    <string name="capitao_name">Vicente Souza</string>
    <string name="capitao_dob">November 17th, 1967</string>
    <string name="capitao_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="capitao_height">86 KG</string>
    <string name="capitao_background">Vicente Souze grew up in Nova Iguacu outside Rio de Janeiro, the youngest of three children. Tenacious and dedicated, Souze joined the Policia Civil after high school. He was quickly recruited by Cooredenadoria de Recursos Especiais (CORE).\n\nDuring a raid on the Terceiro Comando Puro with CORE, Souza was  ambushed as he cleared a house in Senador Camara. Two months later, CORE was able to extract Souza and three other hostages during a rescue operation, however the damage to Souza\'s body was done. \n\nThere were talks of removing him from the field. In the meantime, CORE was looking for field operatives to test new gears, and Souze saw his chance. His stoicism and unique tactical method then turned him into a local icon. \n\nThat\'s when BOPE made him an offer, seeing in him their unit\'s spirit, victory over death. Souza could not turn them down; it meant working in the favela where his gear would lessen casualties.</string>
    <string name="capitao_profile">When Souza was ten, his older brother was killed by a member of the Comando Vermelho. After losing his brother, he dedicated his life to protecting Brazil. He can become fixiated when innocent lives are at stake. This makes him an excellent operative in conditions where there is a high risk for collateral damage. His experience as a hostage has only strengthened his resolve to protect Brazil from the horrors the drug trade inflicts upon its people.</string>
    <string name="capitao_training">Policia Civil \n\nCORE \n\nBOPE</string>
    <string name="capitao_experience">BOPE Captain, Training Officer</string>
    <string name="capitao_notes">His affinity for children and hatred of narcotics can be triggers for obsessive behavior.</string>
    <string name="capitao_gadget_name">TAC MK0</string>
    <string name="capitao_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Crossbow</string>
    <string name="capitao_gadget">Tactical crossbow firing a asphyxiating bolts and micro smoke grenades</string>
    <string name="capitao_gadget_one">Use a glass bolt to deliver a swift and silent assault against hostiles without alerting them to your position. The glass cartridge breaks on impact releasing a gas that ignites the oxygen in the surrounding area. Deliver swift and agile assaults without alerting your opponents of your position.</string>

    <!-- HIBANA -->

    <string name="hibana_name">Yumiko Imagawa</string>
    <string name="hibana_dob">July 12th, 1983</string>
    <string name="hibana_weight">1.73 M</string>
    <string name="hibana_height">57 KG</string>
    <string name="hibana_background">A Nagoya native, Imagawa traveled the world to perfect her skills and technique. She is specialised in paramilitary techniques gained by training with SAS,FBI,SWAT and GIGN, to name a few. From her diverse training she acquired a rare tactical versatility, which includes a proficient in tubular (bus,train and airplane) assaults.
\n\nThe daughter of a local butcher, Imagawa was inspired by her family to practice Kyudo from a young age. This long range weapon marked her entry in martial arts by perfecting her assessment of multiple factors at once while carrying precise, controlled and fluid motions.\n\nHer area of expertise is to gain entry in high risk areas. During her studies at the National Police Academy, she gained the nickname Hibana due to her improvised explosive devices and brilliant leadership skills on the field.\n\nFluent in seven languages and lethal with any weapon, Imagawa was recruited by the Aichi Prefectural Police Department Special Unit, where her diverse techniques and charisma allowed her to move up the ranks quickly.</string>
    <string name="hibana_profile">Imagawa is a natural team builder.Passionate and adaptive, she inspires experts from diverse backgrounds to work together and reach a common goal.</string>
    <string name="hibana_training">National Police Academy: Cadet Course, Course for Experts, Course for Newly Appointed Inspectors.\n\nClose Quarters Combat (CQC) Course in Perthm Australia;\n\nWon the 2011 Combat Team Conference (CTC)</string>
    <string name="hibana_experience">National Police Academy\n\nAichi Prefectural Police Department Special Unit\n\nAssistant Inspector\n\nSpecial Assault Team (SAT)\n\n2003 Beppu Hostage Crisis\n\n2007 Obayashi Hostage Crisis\n\n2015 SAT Joint Traning (Ise Shima Summit)</string>
    <string name="hibana_notes">Participates in numerous Special Operations conferences around the world, and presented a panel on Disaster Reduction in Sendai, Miyagi Prefecture. She also collaborated with FBI SWAT Operator Jordan Trace on Project X-KAIROS</string>
    <string name="hibana_gadget_name">X-KAIROS</string>
    <string name="hibana_gadget_name_byline">40mm Caliber Launcher</string>
    <string name="hibana_gadget">A 40mm grenade launcher firing explosive pellets that can be detonated from distance.</string>
    <string name="hibana_gadget_one">The X-KAIROS - a 40 mm caliber launcher - fires explosive pellets that can be detonated simultaneously from a distance.</string>
    <string name="hibana_gadget_two">Deliver innovative assaults by creating lines of sights, or new pathways!</string>


    <!-- JACKAL -->

    <string name="jackal_name">Ryad Ramirez Al-Hassar</string>
    <string name="jackal_dob">February 29th, 1968</string>
    <string name="jackal_weight">1.90 M</string>
    <string name="jackal_height">78 KG</string>
    <string name="jackal_background">Pushed from one family to the next, Ryad emerged from the foster care system when his older brother, Faisal Ramirez, turned 18 and became his legal guardian.\n\nBlaming his shortcomings for the loss of his older brother, Ramirez decided to join the Policia Nacional. He passed the mandatory ESO (Secondary studies) and became a CNP (Cuerpo Nacional de Policia) at 19 years old. He is still investigating his brother\'s case and to this day, but was unable to find any solid evidence against his brother\'s murderer.\n\nWith strong resolve and broad resourcefulness in difficult terrains, Ramirez joined the Grupo Especial de Operaciones (GEO) to track down HVTs and intercept narcotics shipments.</string>
    <string name="jackal_profile">Suffers from chronic insomnia. Ramirez is at risk of developing acute symptoms such as muscular weariness, hallucinations and/or double vision. He must be monitored closely.</string>
    <string name="jackal_training">Tactical Tracking course for Law Enforcement\n\nTrans Sahara (OEF-TS) - Multinational Training Courses, Counter Tracking Training\n\nCrime Scene Track Interpretation Course\n\nSpecialized Combat Diving Course</string>
    <string name="jackal_experience">Cuerpo Naccional de Policia\n\nGrupo Especial de Operaciones (G.E.O)\n\n2002 tracked a series of HVT for the International Tribunal of former Yugoslavia in The Hague\n\n2004 Madrid train bombing\n2009 Indonesia, Temanggung</string>
    <string name="jackal_notes">None</string>
    <string name="jackal_gadget_name">EYENOX MODEL III</string>
    <string name="jackal_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Tracker</string>
    <string name="jackal_gadget">Tracking Eyewear that locates  targets by revealing and identifying the recent footsteps.</string>
    <string name="jackal_gadget_one">Eyenox Model III was created to offer a mobile tracking device able to both identify and trail a person’s footprints in real-time.</string>
    <string name="jackal_gadget_two">Equipped with advanced computer vision, the Eyenox detects invisible details relating to footfall and weight distribution so that you can identify and stalk your target.</string>

    <!-- Ying -->

    <string name="ying_name">Siu Mei Lin</string>
    <string name="ying_dob">July 12th, 1983</string>
    <string name="ying_weight">1.60 M</string>
    <string name="ying_height">52 KG</string>
    <string name="ying_background">Born in the comfortable Central district of Hong Kong, Siu Mei Lin was a close protection operative before joining the Special Duties Unit (SDU). With her acute reflexes and cunning CQB methods, she took the lead on several VIP and witness protection operations.\n\nHaving deployed an explosive short-range power and combat skills, she joined an elite security service school after graduation. Aiming to become an all-purpose operative, she traveled to a female exclusive training facility in Tel Aviv, Israel. She spent two years there, developing an expertise in firearms and driving maneuvers. Part of Operation High Sun.\nAfter completing her program she returned to Hong Kong, where she ensured the protection of several high risk profiles. In 2008, she reoriented her toward the police force after being involved in a kidnapping situation.\n\nShe was first recruited to review the processes used by the Police Tactical Force\'s Security Wing. During this time, her interest to lead international rescue operations grew, which drove her to apply to the SDU.\n\nAs a Flying Tiger (SDU), she uses her experience in close protection to ensure minimum casualties while leading high risk operations amidst Hong Kong\'s dense urban population.</string>
    <string name="ying_profile">Her easy-going manner allows her to blend in, making her clients and teammates feel both secure and comfortable. Shows potential signs of post-traumatic stress disorder. She admitted having flashbacks of the car crash when she rushes into high risk situations involving a number of civilians. Her extreme driving maneuvers may be a way for her to cope with stress, to assert control over those memories.</string>
    <string name="ying_training">Wing Chun Kung Fu\n\nInternational Security Agency- Tel Aviv Training Center\n\nPolice Tactical Force - Security Wing\n\nSpecial Duties Unit (SDU)</string>
    <string name="ying_experience">2004 Operation High Sun: linked to Operation Eliza Cohen and Shuhrat Kessikbayev\n\n2005 Operation Black Jack: Collaborated with Operator Masaru Enatsu\n\n2008: Abduction of Jyu Victor Cheung: tasked with ensuring the secure delivery of ransom cash to allocated area.\n\n2012 Evacuated Diplomats during a Legislative Council vote</string>
    <string name="ying_notes">In her official report of 2004, Siu mentions a disagreement between herself and Kessikbayev, who she stated "had a complete disregard for civilian lives",which made him questionable asset. According to her file, that situation was only resolved once Cohen stepped in.\n\nShe later in her career also met and collaborated with Masaru "Echo" Enatsu. They were romantically involved from 2005 to 2006.</string>
    <string name="ying_gadget_name">CANDELA DEVICE</string>
    <string name="ying_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Flash Device</string>
    <string name="ying_gadget">Cluster of flash charges that can either be anchored on surfaces or rolled out as grenade</string>
    <string name="ying_gadget_one">The Candela device releases a cluster of flash charges that can either be anchored on surfaces or thrown out as a grenade.</string>


    <!-- ZOFIA -->


    <string name="zofia_name">Zofia Bosak</string>
    <string name="zofia_dob">January 28th, 1981</string>
    <string name="zofia_weight">1.79 M</string>
    <string name="zofia_height">72 KG</string>
    <string name="zofia_background">Born in Wroclaw, Zofia Bosak is the oldest daughter of Jan Bosak, former commander of the Polish Special Forces Unit GROM. While attending her father\'s military high school, she was pressured to perform on every level – a burden her younger sister was not able to cope with. \n\nDuring a school trip to the Masurian Lake District, Zofia was prey to a disturbing prank that almost cost her life. While she played in the lake, three boys from her class took turns trying to drown her, just for \'fun\'. This violent experience marked her with a deep mistrust of others. The following week, she has to sit beside her assailants in class. To deal with her growing anxiety, she decided to push her training further, and ensure she could rely on her skills for protection. Her father agreed to show her more ruthless techniques, given she would never question his methods. \n\nWhen Zofia hit legal age, she enlisted in the army. Among Zofia\'s most notable exploits is a rescue Operation in Guatemala, codenamed Red Agatha. A disastrous tropical storm formed a sinkhole in the middle of the city, swallowing an entire neighbourhood. Zofia was deployed to protect a team of scientists examining the perimeter. During a sudden landfall, she saved a child from disappearing into the abyss. To reward her ability to withstand hardships, Zofia received a medal and was promoted to Second Lieutenant. \n\nThroughout her experiences, Zofia forged a second family overseas. to have more impact on the field, she learned to trust her squad mates with her life, reconsidering the cruel lesson from the incident at Lakeland. Far away from her father\'s brutal training, Zofia let down her walls, developing close ties for the first time. She met her now-husband during a rogue operation in Mali, where they both mistook each other for hostiles.\n\nChallenged by her squad mates on the field, she discovered the true kind of specialist she wanted to become. At the peak of her career, she flew back to Poland for her wedding ceremony. The celebration was kept short, but Zofia quickly returned to Wroclaw for her maternity leave. Her arrival in Poland was soon followed by her father\'s sudden passing. \n\nThe birth of her daughter had a profound effect on Zofia, igniting her need to cocoon with her family – but Ela ignored her sister\'s attempts to reconcile. \n\nZofia returned to the GROM soon after hearing Ela would pass the selection. Except for her attempts to reconnect with her sister, Zofia kept her distance with everyone else. Her squadron noticed this change and wondered if her recent obsession with her father\'s pocket watch was a remnant of grief, or something more. \n\nWhen Ela accepted the prestigious offer to join Team Rainbow, Zofia saw no reason to stay behind. Everything about the GROM now seemed to remind her of her father. \n\nThree months later, Zofia became an official member of Team Rainbow.</string>
    <string name="zofia_profile">Underwent thorough examination, but remains inconclusive. Perhaps too experienced at falsifying test results
Significant divide between the two sisters. \nTheir father had a key role in it. His obvious favoritism towards Zofia is well-known. \n\nWhen asked about their relationship growing up, Zofia kept her answers curt and non-committal.
And yet, very protective of Ela. \n\nRefuses to discuss her father's suicide</string>
    <string name="zofia_training">Cadet Academy: Land Army Military, GROM\n\nSurvive, Evade, Resist, Extract (SERE) training\n\nNight Parachute Dropes on hostile territory and Improvised explosives\n\nGROM Squadron (ZBC) - Specialty unknown</string>
    <string name="zofia_experience">Umm Qasr (2003)\n\nXXXX, Mali (2007)\n\nRed Agatha, Guatemala (2009)</string>
    <string name="zofia_notes">Married, Has a daughter, aged 2.</string>
    <string name="zofia_gadget_name">KS79 LIFELINE</string>
    <string name="zofia_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Breacher and Stun</string>
    <string name="zofia_gadget">Double barrel launcher that can fire both concussion and impact grenades</string>
    <string name="zofia_gadget_one">KS79 LIFELINE makes use of electronically triggered projectile technology that can fire both concussion and impact ammunition.</string>
    <string name="zofia_gadget_two">The concussion ammunition delivers a 170-decibel shockwave that impairs hearing and causes a dizzying effect.</string>

    <!-- DOKKAEBI -->


    <string name="dokkaebi_name">Grace Nam</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_dob">February 2nd, 1988</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_weight">1.69 M</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_height">62 KG</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_background">Grace, named for the incomparable actress Grace Kelly, always broke expectations, even when it meant she stuck out somehow. She scavenged or bought spare components to build her own computers. She played soccer with the neighborhood boys and got into fights with them, but it was her sharp tongue that landed her in trouble with her teachers. She looked and acted like a troublemaker, so they tried to force her to conform to expectations. To survive, Grace learned to soften her image, to better play with and manipulate preconceptions; she bought fake glasses and adopted the geek girl persona. \n\nGrace\'s skills earned a National Scholarship at KAIST (Korean Advanced Institute of Science and Technology), but after graduating decided to join the Army. Her athleticism and daring paid off, and she was assigned to the ROK Army Special Warfare Command before earning a spot in the 9th Special Forces Brigade known as the Ghosts. Despite her unorthodox behavior within the highly disciplined ROK army, she gained notice for her exemplary tech skills and for being highly adaptable to situations. After Grace participated in joint training with Detachment K Green Berets, the American instructors encouraged her to try out with the 707th Special Mission Battalion: White Tigers. \n\nThe White Tigers were a better fit for her skills, but Grace inadvertently butted heads with Major General Kuh, an old guard soldier with political ties all the way up to the Blue House, who followed orders to the letter and expected unflinching loyalty from his subordinates. Kuh made life difficult for Grace, preventing her from exploiting her full potential. \n\nGrace heard about Rainbow during training exercises with the SAS, and it sounded like the opportunity she had been seeking... the chance to contribute through her strengths. She knew that Major General Kuh would never put her on the list, so she did what she always did and thought outside of the box. \n\nNow Dokkaebi is a member of Rainbow much to the surprise of Major General Kuh, who is not happy about it. He wants her drummed out of the White Tigers, but Dokkaebi could not be happier. She is among men and women who reward asymmetrical thinking even though she knows she now has a target on her back. More so, she is sure the other ROK operator, Chul Kyung Hwa, is spying on her. She needs to work twice as hard, but Grace feels twice as motivated now</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_profile">Grace plays with expectation because she wants people to underestimate her, but it is different with Rainbow. Before she knew how to control the situation and was never afraid of failure until the stakes became this critical. Rainbow Six was her most daring stunt and she knows she\'s alienated herself from the Korean military; any slip up and this point will see her drummed out of the military entirely, and this has added pressure to perform, improve, and succeed.</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_training">KAIST \n\n9th Special Forces Brigade\n\nDetachment K Green Berets\n\n707th Special Mission Battalion.</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_experience">Operation Burnt Fuse\n\nROK Cybershield\n\nOperation Deep Vain.</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_notes">Grace is sure that Chul Kyung Hwa was asked to monitor her, and it certainly does not help that he keeps telling her how to behave. In her books, he represents the old school thinking in the ROK Military but she does not seem distracted by her geek persona. It is not a factor with him. She tries to remain civil, but she knows her stuff and does not appreciate him trying to correct her behavior. Grace is on friendly terms with Echo, both of whom connect on matters of technology, but they also get competitive when it comes to outdoing each other in workshop. \n\nGrace utilizes the Ballistic Armor Military Laptop, codenamed Logic Bomb, which she used to hack enemy PDA tactical devices. That program downloads a virus of her making that can bypass firewalls, turning surrounding devices on and emitting a loud buzzing noise to compromise enemy position. The program is short and self erasing to prevent anyone from unraveling her code and building software to counter Logic Bomb.</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_gadget_name">LOGIC BOMB</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_gadget_name_byline">Tactical Hacking Tool</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_gadget">Uploads a virus that forces enemy phones to emit a low buzz that can be overheard, thereby potentially compromising an enemy position.</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_gadget_one">Grace utilizes the Ballistic Armor Military Laptop, codenamed Logic Bomb, which she uses to hack enemy PDA tactical devices.</string>
    <string name="dokkaebi_gadget_two">The program downloads a virus of her making that can bypass firewalls, turning surrounding devices on and emitting a loud noise to compromise an enemy’s position.</string>


    <!-- LION -->


    <!-- FINKA -->


    <!--          DEFENDERS  -->

    <!-- SMOKE -->
    <string name="smoke_name">James Porter</string>
    <string name="smoke_dob">May 14, 1990</string>
    <string name="smoke_weight">1.73 M</string>
    <string name="smoke_height">70 KG</string>
    <string name="smoke_background">Porter was not an academic, although in secondary school, he excelled in science. He took a particular interest in biology and the unit on dissection. During his gap year, Porter enlisted in the British Army, using a fake ID to circumvent parental consent</string>
    <string name="smoke_profile">He is a known thrill seeker with very little regard for his personal safety. He is fearless in battle and can be a great asset for defensive maneuvers, however he seems to enjoy the havoc and chaos of war. He uses a remote detonated dispersal mine filled with a gas of undisclosed contents to impede hostile advances</string>
    <string name="smoke_training">British Army\n\nSAS Operative</string>
    <string name="smoke_experience">After basic training, Porter was stationed in Belfast. Finding the posting a bit dull in the wake of March 2007 treaty, he joined the Army Boxing Team as a middleweight.</string>
    <string name="smoke_notes">None</string>
    <string name="smoke_gadget_name">COMPOUND Z8</string>
    <string name="smoke_gadget_name_byline">Remote Gas Grenade</string>
    <string name="smoke_gadget">Sets remote detonated toxic gas charge.</string>
    <string name="smoke_gadget_one">Detonator</string>
    <string name="smoke_gadget_two">Remote receiver</string>
    <string name="smoke_gadget_three">Double-sided tape allows vertical or horizontal mounting</string>


    <!-- MUTE -->

    <string name="mute_name">Mark Chandar</string>
    <string name="mute_dob">October 11, 1991</string>
    <string name="mute_weight">1.70 M</string>
    <string name="mute_height">80 KG</string>
    <string name="mute_background">Chandar graduated from secondary school at the age of twelve. A science prodigy, he was accepted into the University of Cambridge, Department of Engineering at fourteen after completing an internship at a British tech company during his gap year, working on prototypes for a new security system.</string>
    <string name="mute_profile">Chandar is highly intelligent and analytical. He is used to being the youngest and smartest one in the room. A man of few words, he prefers brevity and clarity to extemporizing. His curt nature is easily misconstrued as rudeness.</string>
    <string name="mute_training">Univeristy of Cambridge:Bachelor of Science, Engineering. \n\nPhD Electrical Engineering\n\nBritain Government\n\nCommunication Headquarters(GCHQ): Signals Intelligence Specialist (sigint)\n\nSAS: sigint Communications and Technology</string>
    <string name="mute_experience">GCHQ Prototype engineer\n\nSAS Prototype engineer</string>
    <string name="mute_notes">Cyber counter terrorism unit, monitor hacktivist groups.\n\nPortions of  file redacted</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget_name">MONI</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget_name_byline">GC90 Signal Disruptor</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget">Jams communications for remotely detonated gadgets or drones in range.</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget_one">Collapsible antennas</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget_two">Device can be planted on floors</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget_three">Digital display</string>
    <string name="mute_gadget_four">Activation levers</string>

    <!-- CASTLE -->

    <string name="castle_name">Miles Campbell</string>
    <string name="castle_dob">September 20, 1980</string>
    <string name="castle_weight">1.85 M</string>
    <string name="castle_height">95.3 KG</string>
    <string name="castle_background">Castle graduated from California State Los Angeles with a bachelor\'s degree in Science and Criminal Justice and promptly joined the LAPD. After five years, he was assigned to the LAPD SWAT team where he excelled at for three years before being transferred to the FBI. Once two years had passed, his career had taken a natural progression as he was reassigned to the FBI SWAT team. He brings an expertise in defense and reinforcement to Team Rainbow, ever ready to deploy his signature reinforced barricades</string>
    <string name="castle_profile">Castle has a knack for putting people at ease, always appearing comfortable despite the situation. He constantly strives to make sure that those around him are taken care of and feel safe and is highly protective of people close to him. Castle studies languages as a hobby, being able to speak Latin, Spanish, and Korean.</string>
    <string name="castle_training">California State University, Los Angeles (Cal State LA): Bachelor of Science, Criminal Justice\n\nLAPD: Police Officer, SWAT\n\nFBI: Field Agent, SWAT</string>
    <string name="castle_experience">FBI New Operator Training School (NOTS)\n\nMultiple cross departmental training sessions with Federal and International law enforcement including SAS GIGN and GSG9\n\nFBI SWAT WMD training</string>
    <string name="castle_notes">Studies languages as a hobby. Speaks Latin,Spanish and Korean.</string>
    <string name="castle_gadget_name">ARMOR PANEL</string>
    <string name="castle_gadget_name_byline">UTP1-Universal Tactical Panel</string>
    <string name="castle_gadget">Sets bulletproof barricades that are more resistant than standard ones.</string>
    <string name="castle_gadget_one">Rollable armor panel</string>
    <string name="castle_gadget_two">Polyethylene, ballistic fabric, and boron ceramic micro-plates</string>

    <!-- PULSE -->

    <string name="pulse_name">Jack Estrada</string>
    <string name="pulse_dob">October 11, 1984</string>
    <string name="pulse_weight">1.92 M</string>
    <string name="pulse_height">104 KG</string>
    <string name="pulse_background">Born to Cynthia Estrada and Mark Peterson on Seymore Johnson Air Force Base, Pulse was raised as a military brat. Following his mother\'s footsteps, Pulse became an intelligence officer.\n\nIn 2007, Pulse became an intern for the FBI biometrics program, moving from the lab to active duty in 2010 where he was invited to join the FBI SWAT team. Pulse\'s work with the FBI biometrics program allowed him to blend his background in communications and biochemistry to a powerful effect. His innate ability to read people made him a natural negotiator. Pulse's Heartbeat Sensor first saw use in the Michael Somerset abduction.</string>
    <string name="pulse_profile">Due to his constant relocation from base to base, Jack became fascinated by the microscopic variances that comprise identity. As a result, he became adept at recognizing micro-expressions and delineating a person\'s history based on their speech patterns and physicality.</string>
    <string name="pulse_training">Purdue University: Bachelor of Science, Forensics. Master of Science: Biometrics\n\nFBI Biometrics Intern\n\nFBI Biometrics Operator\n\nFBI SWAT Negotiator</string>
    <string name="pulse_experience">In 2007, Jack became an intern for the FBI biometrics program. Moving from the lab to active duty in 2017, where jack was invited to join the FBI SWAT team.\n\nHis innate ability to read people made him a natural negotiator.
</string>
    <string name="pulse_notes">Lead negotiator, Michael Somerset abduction, first operation to utilize Heart Sensor prototype.</string>
    <string name="pulse_gadget_name">HEARTBEAT SENSOR</string>
    <string name="pulse_gadget_name_byline">HB-5 Cardiac Sensor</string>
    <string name="pulse_gadget">Detects heartbeats at short distance through short distance through obstacles</string>
    <string name="pulse_gadget_one">This heartbeat detector can read thermal signatures through walls and other obstacles</string>

    <!-- DOC -->

    <string name="doc_name">Gustave Kateb</string>
    <string name="doc_dob">September 16, 1977</string>
    <string name="doc_weight">1.77 M</string>
    <string name="doc_height">79 KG</string>
    <string name="doc_background">Kateb grew up in an affluent family, in Paris 16th arrondissement. At twenty, he abandoned a potentially prominent private medical practice in favor of a career with the French Defense Health Service. He is certified to practice in ten countries "Doctors Without Borders"</string>
    <string name="doc_profile">Gustave Kateb is cut from a rare cloth: a genuine altruist, a true believer in making the world a safer place for his fellow man. A volunteer for Doctors Without Borders and medical officer for the Brigade des Forces Speciales Terre, he is a proficient field medic who carries a Stim Pistol allowing him to revive downed teammates from a distance.</string>
    <string name="doc_training">Universite Paris Descartes: Bachelor of Science, Health: Master Toxicology and Ecotoxicology; Doctorate Medicine, Toxicology, Chemistry, Imagery (MTCI) \n\nFrench Defence Health Service \n\nArmy Specia Forces Brigade \n\nGIGN</string>
    <string name="doc_experience">Two tours of duty\n\nDoctors without Borders, certified to practice in ten countries</string>
    <string name="doc_notes">None</string>
    <string name="doc_gadget_name">HEALING SYRINGE</string>
    <string name="doc_gadget_name_byline">MPD-0 Stim Pistol</string>
    <string name="doc_gadget">Fires a hypodermic shot to revive himself or teammates from a distance. Can also provide a temporary boost.</string>
    <string name="doc_gadget_one">Handheld, trigger-operated pistol</string>
    <string name="doc_gadget_two">1mg dose of epinephrine, in a saline solution</string>
    <string name="doc_gadget_three">The pistol is powered by a pressurized CO2 canister</string>

    <!-- ROOK -->

    <string name="rook_name">Julien Nizan</string>
    <string name="rook_dob">January 6, 1990</string>
    <string name="rook_weight">1.75 M</string>
    <string name="rook_height">63 KG</string>
    <string name="rook_background">In school, Nizan excelled at athletics specifically in Track and Field. The youngest son of a working-class family, he enlisted in the Gendarmerie Nationale at eighteen and found himself assigned to the Highway Patrol unit. During basic training, Nizan discovered his aptitude for firearms, a skill that he would continue to develop and master over them during his time with the Gendarmerie Nationale. His skill with a rifle eventually attracted the attention of the GIGN</string>
    <string name="rook_profile">Nizan is idealistic and trusting. He can be impulsive and must self-regulate in order to remain on task. When his focus is clear, he is decisive and driven to complete the task at hand.</string>
    <string name="rook_training">Gendarmerie Nationale\n\nGIGN</string>
    <string name="rook_experience">GIGN Marksmanship champion</string>
    <string name="rook_notes">Performs trust exercises with all new recruits\n\nFluent in English, studied with an American Professor at Secondary School</string>
    <string name="rook_gadget_name">ARMOR PACK</string>
    <string name="rook_gadget_name_byline">R1N "Rhino" Armor</string>
    <string name="rook_gadget">Dropes a supply bag full of armor plates for his team to use</string>
    <string name="rook_gadget_one">Armor plates are stored in a light weight sturdy satcheld for rapid field deployment</string>
    <string name="rook_gadget_two">A multi-hit boron ceramic plate with a special spall-stop coating, and a back-face deformation (BFD) plate</string>


    <!-- KAPKAN -->

    <string name="kapkan_name">Maxim Basuda</string>
    <string name="kapkan_dob">May 14, 1979</string>
    <string name="kapkan_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="kapkan_height">68 KG</string>
    <string name="kapkan_background">Born and raised in Kovrov, Basuda is the eldest of three sons of parents who were factory workers. Hoping to escape a grueling life in the factory, he enlisted with the Ministry of Internal Affairs and was sent to Naryan-Mar, a small sea and river port town on the Barents Sea. Basuda became an avid hunter and trapper during his time in the Arctic Circle, before being transferred to Beslan in 2002.</string>
    <string name="kapkan_profile">Basuda is a self-sufficient realist. He has seen the harsh reality of the world and does not allow that to hinder his ability to act. He\'s fascinated by psychology; what allows one creature to become a hunter and the other prey.</string>
    <string name="kapkan_training">Ministry of Internal Affairs, Police Officer\n\nSpetznaz</string>
    <string name="kapkan_experience">Beslan School Siege\n\nREDACTED</string>
    <string name="kapkan_notes">One of only a handful of officers to walk away rfom the Beslan School Siege. Extensive Collection of weapons and survival gear. Designs and Builds snares and traps as hobby.</string>
    <string name="kapkan_gadget_name">EDD MK II</string>
    <string name="kapkan_gadget_name_byline">Entry Denial Device</string>
    <string name="kapkan_gadget">Sets booby traps on windows and door frames</string>
    <string name="kapkan_gadget_one">May be mounted into windows and door frames.</string>
    <string name="kapkan_gadget_two">Packed C4 charge.</string>

    <!-- TACHANKA -->

    <string name="tachanka_name">Alexandr Senaviev</string>
    <string name="tachanka_dob">November 3, 1967</string>
    <string name="tachanka_weight">1.83 M</string>
    <string name="tachanka_height">99.8 KG</string>
    <string name="tachanka_background">Born into a Red Army family, Senaviev enlisted when he turned eighteen. After the Soviet Union pulled out of Afghanistan, Senaviev was transferred into the Spetsnaz shortly before the collapse of the Union.</string>
    <string name="tachanka_profile">Calm in crises. Alex harbors a joyous, if acerbic outlook. He has a limited social filter, which has gotten him into trouble in the past.</string>
    <string name="tachanka_training">Soviet Army\n\nSpetznaz</string>
    <string name="tachanka_experience">Soviet War in Afghanistan\n\nChechnya\n\nGeorgia</string>
    <string name="tachanka_notes">A collector of Soviet era weaponry, he prefers simple designs proven to be effective, over the modern experimental technology and warfare.</string>
    <string name="tachanka_gadget_name">MOUNTED LMG</string>
    <string name="tachanka_gadget_name_byline">RP-46 Degtyaryov Machine Gun</string>
    <string name="tachanka_gadget">Deploys a Mounted LMG with a ballistic shield protecting the head from frontal shots</string>
    <string name="tachanka_gadget_one">The tripod allows the weapon to fire from a standing position</string>
    <string name="tachanka_gadget_two">Original circular flat pan magazines</string>

    <!-- JAGER -->

    <string name="jager_name">Marius Streicher</string>
    <string name="jager_dob">March 9, 1978</string>
    <string name="jager_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="jager_height">69 KG</string>
    <string name="jager_background">Raised by his uncle who was a mechanic for what later became the Bundespolizei (BPOL) Aviation Group after reunification, Streicher joined BPOL as a helicopter technician. He began designing defensive weapon systems, including a ground-based Active Defense System (ADS) prototype that caught the attention of the GSG-9. A veteran of the GSG-9 anti-piracy ops in the Indian Ocean, he was later recruited to Team Rainbow</string>
    <string name="jager_profile">Streicher is highly creative and curious, with a strong desire to serve. He has a tendency to lack humility. Though he has a remarkable affinity for complex machinery, he is not adept at reading social cues. Coupled with his boisterous tendencies he can be a bit abrasive.</string>
    <string name="jager_training">Karlsruhe Institute of Technology: Bachelor of Science, Aerospace Engineering\n\nBundespolizei: Helicopter Technician, Weapons Maintenance\n\nGSG9: Technical Advisor\n\nGSG9: Operator</string>
    <string name="jager_experience">GSG9 Basic and Advanced training\n\nCQB training for operations at sea\n\nInvolved in anti piracy ops</string>
    <string name="jager_notes">None</string>
    <string name="jager_gadget_name">ADS-MK IV "MAGPIE"</string>
    <string name="jager_gadget_name_byline">Active Defender System</string>
    <string name="jager_gadget">Uses an Active Defense system to intercept grenades before they detonate</string>
    <string name="jager_gadget_one">Wall or floor mounter</string>
    <string name="jager_gadget_two">Four surveillance cameras allow for precise targeting</string>
    <string name="jager_gadget_three">Full range grenade launcher</string>


    <!-- BANDIT -->

    <string name="bandit_name">Dominic Brunsmeier</string>
    <string name="bandit_dob">August 13, 1974</string>
    <string name="bandit_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="bandit_height">95 KG</string>
    <string name="bandit_background">Brunsmeier and his twin brother Cedrick joined the Bundesgrenzschutz (BGS) the day after their eighteenth birthday. Stationed with border patrol he would spend his first year getting accustomed to following orders and filing paperwork</string>
    <string name="bandit_profile">A prankster, Brunsmeier honors and humiliates his brother\'s memory each time he deploys the Crude Electrical Device (CED), the weapon responsible for Cedrick\'s early retirement from the BGS. Resourceful and adaptive, Brunsmeier relies on his cunning for survival</string>
    <string name="bandit_training">Bundepolizei formerly known as Bundesgrenzschutz (BGS)\n\nWeiterstadt Red Army Faction\n\nGSG9 Undercover Agent Hannover Hells Angels\n\nGSG9</string>
    <string name="bandit_experience">In his second year with BGS, Brunsmeier was assigned to joint task force aims at quelling the growing threat of the Red Army Faction (RAF). in 2006 he was  recruited by GSG9 to go undercover, where he would spend four years embedded with the Hannover Chapter of the hells angels</string>
    <string name="bandit_notes">None</string>
    <string name="bandit_gadget_name">CED-1 (CRUDE ELECTRICAL DEVICE)</string>
    <string name="bandit_gadget_name_byline">Shock Wire</string>
    <string name="bandit_gadget">Sets up Crude Electrical Device that electrifies other gadgets and damages anything that comes in contact</string>
    <string name="bandit_gadget_one">Taser is wired to the battery</string>
    <string name="bandit_gadget_two">Car battery</string>
    <string name="bandit_gadget_three">Copper cage with jumper cables</string>


    <!-- FROST -->

    <string name="frost_name">Tine Lin Tsang</string>
    <string name="frost_dob">May 4, 1985</string>
    <string name="frost_weight">1.72 M</string>
    <string name="frost_height">58 KG</string>
    <string name="frost_background">Tsang grew up in Vancouver, British Columbia. When she turned eighteen Tsang enlisted with the Royal Canadian Air Force (RCAF), and was sent to the Royal Military College of Canada (RMC) as an Officer Cadet. After completing her bachelor\'s degree and officer training, Tsang was stationed at CFB Comox with the Joint Rescue Coordination Centre Victoria(JRCC Victoria).</string>
    <string name="frost_profile">Tsang is an extremely focused individual who meticulously plans out every move she makes. When she sets her eyes on a goal, there is little that can stop her. Tsang is patient and never takes shortcuts.</string>
    <string name="frost_training">Royal Military College, Kingston : Bachelor of Science, Mechanical Engineering\n\nRoyal Canadian Air Force Combat Systems Officer-Training\n\nRCAF, JRCC Victoria : Combat Systems Officer\n\nJTF2 Assault</string>
    <string name="frost_experience">A search and rescue tech, Tsang\'s ability to quickly solve complex problems with simple solutions and remain composed under extreme pressure made her an excellent candidate for JTF2.</string>
    <string name="frost_notes">An avid hunter, Tsang has used leg-hold traps to capture prey from raccoons to mountain lions on Vancouver Island.</string>
    <string name="frost_gadget_name">STERLING MK2 LHT (WELCOME MAT)</string>
    <string name="frost_gadget_name_byline">Spring Loaded Leg-Hold </string>
    <string name="frost_gadget">Uses a mechanical trap to incapacitate enemies</string>
    <string name="frost_gadget_one">The rubber mat and concealed metal jaws are bolted in place. When the pressure plate is engaged, two sets of jaws at ankle and shin height deploy, locking the person in place.</string>
    <string name="frost_gadget_two">Requires two people to release the jaws and reset the trap.</string>


    <!-- VALKYRIE -->

    <string name="valkyrie_name">Meghan J. Castellano</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_dob">July 21, 1986</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_weight">1.70 M</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_height">57 KG</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_background">An Olympic hopeful in the 200-meter backstroke, Castellano split her time between the pool and the army base, where her father was a training officer. Her junior year, Castellano broke her arm in a car accident, putting an end to her Olympic ambitions. After high school, she enlisted in the Navy. Serving four years, before attending college on the Veterans Affairs bill, upon graduation she returned to the Navy as a career intelligence officer.</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_profile">Castellano is singularly focused. She is driven and does not know how to give up on the goal easily. She will do whatever it takes to accomplish the mission in the most seamless and effective way possible.</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_training">NAVY Intelligence Specialist\n\nUniversity of California, San Diego : Bachelor of Science, Computer Science\n\nNAVY Intelligence Officer\n\nSEAL's Training (BU D/ NSW/ Basic Conditioning/ Combat Diving/ LWT/ SQT)\n\nNAVY SEAL</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_experience">After Basic training Valkyrie was assigned to the 10th Fleet\'s Intelligence team.</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_notes">None</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_gadget_name">GYRO CAM MK2</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_gadget_name_byline">Gyroscope Mounted Fisheye Sticky Camera</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_gadget">Can setup Black Eye cameras, feed accessible by whole team via observation tools</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_gadget_one">Encased in a tinted silicone ball, coated in micro-suction cups, the quick deploy camera maintains a clear view thanks to the internal gyroscope that dictates the angle of the lens.The suction cups allow the camera to adhere to any surface, while the gyroscope mounted lens stabilises the camera angle and focus.</string>
    <string name="valkyrie_gadget_two">The live video feed is available to all operators.</string>


    <!-- CAVEIRA -->

    <string name="caveira_name">Taina Pereira</string>
    <string name="caveira_dob">October 15, 1989</string>
    <string name="caveira_weight">1.55 M</string>
    <string name="caveira_height">73 KG</string>
    <string name="caveira_background">Born seventh in a family of ten boys, Pereira had to be resourceful in order to get what she wants. Little of her childhood is known apart from the meager pension her mother received after her father died. She was six years old when the Pereira family was forced to move to a poor neighborhood in the outskirts of the São Paulo state.\nShe only caught the authorities\' attention when she was 16, after her mother reported that she had been missing. A year later, Pereira was arrested miles away on robbery charges in Rio de Janeiro. Remaining poised and displaying intellect throughout the process, Pereira impressed the judge in charge of her case. He was lenient towards her age and character, which, he claimed, showed potential for social-educational reform. He gave Pereira the choice between entering a juvenile reformatory (FEBEM) and working with BOPE in Rio de Janeiro\nSensing protection for her deviant predisposition, Pereira accepted to become a BOPE criminal informant.</string>
    <string name="caveira_profile">Pereira excels at extracting information from suspects. Albeit using controversial methods undermining BOPE protocol, she was a key interrogator during the 2010 Rio de Janeiro Security Crisis. Her brutal behavior on the field suggests she may be suffering from an anti-social personality disorder. However, the results of all the tests conducted were inconclusive.</string>
    <string name="caveira_training">Policia Civil\n\nBOPE</string>
    <string name="caveira_experience">Criminal informant\n\nKey interrogator during the 2010 Rio de Janeiro Security Crisis, Assault on Complexo do Alemao.</string>
    <string name="caveira_notes">Requires further psychological testing to confirm she is stable BOPE asset</string>
    <string name="caveira_gadget_name">LUISON</string>
    <string name="caveira_gadget_name_byline">PRB92 with a Modified Silencer</string>
    <string name="caveira_gadget">Caveira\'s predatory stealth, the "Silent Step" allows her to lurk on her prey, almost inaudible, until its too late</string>
    <string name="caveira_gadget_one">"The “Luison” is wrapped in a rock-based mineral fiber to both insulate and soundproof the silencer. This weapon allows Caveira to incapacitate her target discreetly and conduct an interrogation.</string>
    <string name="caveira_gadget_two">The “Luison” is not only formidable to neutralize your opponent while remaining undetected; it also ensures that no one gets away.</string>

    <!-- ECHO -->

    <string name="echo_name">Masaru Enatsu</string>
    <string name="echo_dob">October 31, 1980</string>
    <string name="echo_weight">1.80 M</string>
    <string name="echo_height">72 KG</string>
    <string name="echo_background">Masaru Enatsu grew up in Suginami City, Tokyo. This heavily populated city center is home to several animation studios and technology companies. At 16 years old, Enatsu was already challenging the robotics field by creating autonomous flying robots capable of search-and-rescue missions in highly difficult conditions. Two years later, he won the International Aerial Robotics Competition (IARC) and is known as having pushed the limits of what flying robots could accomplish.\n\nEnatsu was noticed by the National Police Security Bureau during his studies in Science and Engineering at the Tokyo Metropolitan University. Enticed to test his devices on the field, he entered the National Police Academy. A year later, he joined the Tokyo Metropolitan, Police Department Special Unit.\n\nEfficiency-obsessed and blunt, Enatsu is a talented officer despite his apathetic nature. In the wake of Nagoya's hostage crisis in 2007, Enatsu decided to transfer to the Aichi Prefectural Police Department Special Unit.</string>
    <string name="echo_profile">Singularly focused, Enatsu\'s blunt communication style divides group harmony. His tendency to dismiss feedback has kept him from advancing to a higher rank.</string>
    <string name="echo_training">Science and Engineering Graduate at Tolqfo Metropolitan University\n\nCollaborated with the Research Centre for Space Science\n\nNational Police Academy Cadet Course</string>
    <string name="echo_experience">Tokyo Metropolitan Police Officer\n\nSecurity Police Division\n\nSpecial Assault Team (SAT)\n\n2007 Machida Hostage Crisis\n\n2015 SAT Joint Training (Ise Shima Summit)</string>
    <string name="echo_notes">His vacillation between idleness and excessive work is closely monitored since his transfer to the Aichi unit. Tests have revealed a tendency for cognitive over stimulation resulting from obsessional distractions and impulses. Further testing is required.</string>
    <string name="echo_gadget_name">YOKAI</string>
    <string name="echo_gadget_name_byline">Unmanned Hovering Vehicle</string>
    <string name="echo_gadget">Hovering drone that releases disorienting sonic burst. Yokai also transmits a video feed to the Operator.</string>
    <string name="echo_gadget_one">Equipped with an acoustic hailing device, this signature drone can fire ultrasonic bursts that disorient all targets in a given perimeter. Yokai also transmits a video feed to Echo, who keeps his immediate perimeter secure.</string>
    <string name="echo_gadget_two">Embrace the power of technology and embody a turret Defender who can both hold up the siege and support roamers.</string>


    <!-- MIRA -->

    <string name="mira_name">Elena Maria Alvarez Del Manzano</string>
    <string name="mira_dob">November 18TH, 1971</string>
    <string name="mira_weight">1.78 M</string>
    <string name="mira_height">60 KG</string>
    <string name="mira_background">Working alongside her father in his mechanics store from a young age, Álvarez can find the weaker spot on any machinery and turn it into an edge. She joined the police force Cuerpo Nacional de Policía so that she could be of service to those in need of protection, and thus serve her country.\n\nProving to have stellar strength, endurance and knowledge of vehicles sparked her progress in the ballistic field. She joined the Grupo Especial de Operaciones (GEO) to develop and test bulletproof materials on the field as well as enhancing bridging vehicles.</string>
    <string name="mira_profile">Abandoned by her mother at birth, she was raised by her father in Madrid. Being an only child, she found her purpose working for the family business.</string>
    <string name="mira_training">Specialized in armoring process for ballistic protection\n\nDesign overlap systems on vehicle openings and armor plates layering</string>
    <string name="mira_experience">Cuerpo Nacional de Policia\n\nGrupo Especial de Operaciones (G.E.O)\n\nCompeted at the SWAT EU CQB</string>
    <string name="mira_notes">Following Operation Blue Orion, the two Operators Eliza Cohen and Alvarez have been persistent rivals. Further investigation is required to assess If such tension could become a risk in future cooperative missions.</string>
    <string name="mira_gadget_name">Black Mirror</string>
    <string name="mira_gadget_name_byline">One Way Glass</string>
    <string name="mira_gadget">Deploys a one way bulletproof mirror on breakable and reinforced walls. Also can be ejected to create a murder hole.</string>
    <string name="mira_gadget_one">A specialized laminated glass, which when deployed with oxyacetylene can carve out a one-way mirror on any wall.</string>
    <string name="mira_gadget_two">If the air pressure is disrupted, however, the glass is ejected and creates a daring opening for both defenders and attackers.</string>

    <!-- LESION -->

    <string name="lesion_name">Liu Tze Long</string>
    <string name="lesion_dob">July 2nd, 1972</string>
    <string name="lesion_weight">1.74 M</string>
    <string name="lesion_height">82 KG</string>
    <string name="lesion_background">Born in Junk Bay, Liu Tze Long still lives in a public housing estate not far from this area. He was raised by his father, who worked for a ship breaking company and often pulled double shifts. During these years, Liu would stay at the shipyard and help him dismantle obsolete ships for scrapping.\n\nAs the ship breaking business began to dwindle out, Liu and his father took some demolition jobs under the table. It all came to a stop when Liu\'s father injured his back. Liu was 19 and could not support them both with his own income. Quickly crumbling under debts, he needed money fast.\n\nDuring that time, China sought some volunteers to undertake mine clearance in the provices of Yunnan and Guangxi. Liu answered the call and worked for two years at defusing hazardous ammunitions.\n\nWith ample experience in demolition and mine disposal, he returned to Hong Kong to join the Explosive Ordnance Disposal Bureau. Soon after, he joined the Special Duties Unit (SDU) to deal with Chemical, Biological, Radiological and Nuclear terrorist threats.</string>
    <string name="lesion_profile">Fell in an oil tank while scavenging an old ship when he was 10 years old. Trying to break free, he ingested a significant amount of water seethed with toxins. Since the tank walls were ripped he managed to break free, but not unscarred. Liu is highly resilient to physical hardships. His mental strength is what set him apart from younger candidates. He was one of the 3 other recruits who were able to withstand the extended version of SAS Resistance to Interrogation Program.\n\nN.B. Admitted having detected the tang of oily waters during intense episodes of his Resistance Interrogation training</string>
    <string name="lesion_training">1992-1994 Mine Clearance Duty\n\nHong Kong Explosive Ordnance Disposal Bureau Chemical, Biological, Radiological and Nuclear (CBRN) Defense\n\nSpecial Duties Unit (SDU)\n\nExtensive Resistance to Interrogation Program.</string>
    <string name="lesion_experience">2009 Hong Kong Acid Attacks\n\n2010 0peration Green Viper, Indonesia and Macau.</string>
    <string name="lesion_notes">Resistant to a series of substances and opioids, including morphione. Consult medical file for more details.</string>
    <string name="lesion_gadget_name">GU MINE</string>
    <string name="lesion_gadget_name_byline">Poison Needles</string>
    <string name="lesion_gadget">Cloaked toxic mines injecting a compound which injures opponents and limits their speed</string>
    <string name="lesion_gadget_one">Gu mines were inspired by the sharp punji sticks used during the Vietnam War. Rubbed with toxic plants or feces, the stakes served to slow down enemy troops by causing severe infections in their camp.</string>
    <string name="lesion_gadget_two">Similarly, Gu mines inject a toxin that injure your opponent and limit their speed.</string>

    <!-- ELA -->

    <string name="ela_name">Elzbieta Bosak</string>
    <string name="ela_dob">November 8th, 1985</string>
    <string name="ela_weight">1.73M</string>
    <string name="ela_height">68 KG</string>
    <string name="ela_background">Born in Wroclaw, Elżbieta Bosak is the youngest daughter of Jan Bosak, former commander of the Polish Special Forces unit GROM.\n\nExperiencing some difficulties while attending a military high school, Ela left Poland behind after graduation. In Berlin, she studied Fine Arts, but her interest started to fade as the appeal of her old life slowly caught up with her. During her stay there, she made the acquaintance of the owner of a small private military company, who made her a job offer. Craving the adventure and financial independence, Ela accepted.\n\nWorking as a PMC in Iraq, Ela gained a reputation. Known to possess an impressive range of abilities, her attitude was the only obstacle standing in her way. While she was seen as a prized addition to any squad, her employers monitored her closely to investigate reports of authority issues. Four years into her deployment, she received the first news from home, which stated that her father had taken his own life.\n\nA few month's after her father's death, Ela terminated her contract and started training to pass the GROM selection as a civilian. Impressed by her determination and prowess on the field, the GROM saw in her a rare opportunity. Amidst the Polish Forces, she developed an expertise in Countering Threat Networks (CTN) and helped design advanced Exploitation methods to extract intel on a target's intentions and supply routes.\n\nOne of her most well-known ventures is Operation Orange Sky. Joined by Valkyrie, SEAL's intel expert, Ela spent months infiltrating a warlord's inner circle before dismantling his network without harming a single civilian.</string>
    <string name="ela_profile">Independent, creative, and rebellious, Elzbieta is intimate with the risks involved with her particular role, having suffered many losses in Iraq. The sudden death of her father provided her with a profound need of purpose. Elzbieta internalized the belief that she must prove posthumously her worth to her father and make amends. She uses her memory of him to push herself to unrealistic standards and to lead high-risk operations.</string>
    <string name="ela_training">Survive, Evade, Resist, Extract (SERE) training\n\nConduct of battle damage assessment (BDA)\n\nPrivate Military Contractor\n\nInsurgency Operations\n\nGROM Squadron (ZBC)-Specialty unknown</string>
    <string name="ela_experience">Seizing the Mukarayin Dam (2003)\n\nBaghdad International Airport (2003-2005)\n\nOperation Black Spade (2006)\n\nOperation Orange Sky (2007)</string>
    <string name="ela_notes">Potential for latent authority issues. Can be trumped by her need of validation. It is recommended to emphasize prestige when assigning her an operation. For additional information on this topic, please refer to Second Lieutenant (2nd Lt).</string>
    <string name="ela_gadget_name">GRZMOT MINE</string>
    <string name="ela_gadget_name_byline">Concussion Mines</string>
    <string name="ela_gadget">Concussion proximity mines that can be anchored on surfaces, impairing hearing and causing a dizzying effect</string>
    <string name="ela_gadget_one">Inspired by the 1939 anti-tank Polish grenades used by the iconic Cichociemny during WWII, the sticky Grzmot mines can be anchored on surfaces, impairing hearing and causing a dizzying effect.</string>
    <string name="ela_gadget_two">These concussion mines are triggered upon proximity, affecting anyone within its radius.</string>


    <!-- VIGIL -->
    <string name="vigil_name">Chul Kyung Hwa</string>
    <string name="vigil_dob">January 17TH, 1984</string>
    <string name="vigil_weight">1.73 M</string>
    <string name="vigil_height">73 KG</string>
    <string name="vigil_background">Chul Kyung Hwa doesn\'t remember much of his childhood, only that his family was escaping across Asia as refugees? Or were they criminals? He remembers his older brother drowning during a river crossing. He remembers the safe house where they stayed trapped for over a month in near silence. He remembers their train ride when soldiers arrested two fellow defectors. He remembers his sick mother slowing them all down during the jungle crossing. He remembers leaving her behind as his father told him not to cry, not to make a noise and alert the armed patrols.\n\nThroughout it all, everyone impressed upon Chul Kyung that anything he said or any strange behavior would get them caught... it was life or death. So he buried his emotions deep, lest he betray his parents and be responsible for their capture; he became a stone to the outside world.\n\nGaining asylum in South Korea, it was not the happy life they\'d envisioned. The loss of his family proved too much for Chul Kyung\'s father, who committed suicide, leaving his son an orphan. Chul Kyung remained a stone, never showing emotion, never betraying his inner thoughts.\n\nChul Kyung was adopted into the Hwa family, who believed it best if he forget his past, which started by changing his full name to Chul Kyung Hwa. Chul Kyung was actively encouraged to forget his real name and he obliged. It was another form of camouflage. He grew up in a system of rules and codes of conduct, and they provided him with a reason to be stoic, to follow orders. He could hide behind the rules.\n\nChul Kyung wanted to give back to South Korea, the country that took him in, and he entered the ROK Navy, proving the exemplary sailor. He earned himself a berth in the ROKN UDT/SEALs, not only passing with distinction, but becoming such an exemplary operator in the course of his service that he was handpicked by the 707th Special Mission Battalion: White Tigers. He was diligent, methodical, and tenacious, albeit quiet. Naturally, his status as the child of defectors was not shared with his fellow soldiers to better give him a fair shot, but when South Korea was given an opportunity to send two operators into Rainbow, Chul Kyung was at the top of the list.</string>
    <string name="vigil_profile">Chul Kyung carries the scars of his childhood, where the only safe haven from the uncertainty of escape was to hide deep inside himself and become a stone. While a highly effective and competent by-the-numbers operator, it\'s made him highly uncomfortable in social situations. He is anxious when it comes to his own body language and expressions, how others might interpret his actions. He feels exposed, an open book that betrays all his secrets. Chul Kyung is most comfortable wearing his ballistic mask, where he feels he can actually breathe and hide another layer of protection.</string>
    <string name="vigil_training">ROK Navy\n\nROKN UDT / SEALS\n\n707th Special Mission Battalion</string>
    <string name="vigil_experience">Afghanistan\n\nZaytun Operations on Kurdistan\n\nCheonghae Anti-Piracy Task Group</string>
    <string name="vigil_notes">Despite appearances, Chul Kyung\'s attempts to keep Grace on her best behavior isn\'t an attempt to spare South Korea embarrassment, He knows she\'s made Some enemies In the ROK Military who want to see her gone. He wants to make sure he has nothing negative to report because he knows she values her position in Rainbow as greatly as he does, albeit for different reasons, While he may disagree with Grace\'s approach, he sees her rights and freedoms as the very things he swore to protect, Otherwise, he confides In Blackbeard, having trained under him during Joint training exercise, and has somehow become a friendly target of Mute, who tells Chul Kyung that he\'s too quiet.</string>
    <string name="vigil_gadget_name">ELECTRONIC RENDERING CLOAK (ERC-7)</string>
    <string name="vigil_gadget_name_byline">Video Signal Disruptor</string>
    <string name="vigil_gadget">Vigil scans surrounding devices to wipe his image from cameras and drones</string>
    <string name="vigil_gadget_one">Chul Kyung\’s quiet lethality in the field allows him to rely on his Electronic Rendering Cloak (ERC-7) to remain undetected.</string>
    <string name="vigil_gadget_two">The ERC-7 uses Diminished Reality technology to remove perceivable stimuli from its direct environment. Vigil carries a prototype in his backpack, which scans surrounding electronic devices and wipes his image from any cameras in view.</string>


    <!-- LION -->

    <string name="lion_name">Olivier Flament</string>
    <string name="lion_dob">August 19TH, 1985</string>
    <string name="lion_weight">1.85 M</string>
    <string name="lion_height">87 KG</string>
    <string name="lion_background">Olivier was born to a conservative, well-to-do family. His parents and older sister,Sophie, were in medicine and devout Catholics, but he bucked against their accomplishments and their faith. He was smart and arrogant, but he believed rebellion was a better use of his intellect. It was fun to act against expectation,to drink and party... At least it was until he got his girlfriend, Claire, pregnant.\n\nHe tried to convince Claire to get an abortion, but she refused. Once his parents found out about the pregnancy, they kicked him out of the house ; it was the last straw in a string of bad behavior. Depressed, Olivier went on a drug and alcohol-fueled bender, getting trashed enough to land in the hospital. That was his wakeup call. He was 18 and nearly homeless, so he joined the French Army out of desperation. He needed purpose.\n\nMilitary life was hard but rewarding. Olivier took solace in purpose and struggled to break old habits. He started sending money to Claire to support their newborn son even though she did not want to see Olivier. He became a second-level in-combat rescuer, and joined the 2nd Dragoon Regiment in their role as a CBRN reaction force. He also developed a close relationship with the regiments Catholic Chaplain, Bertrand, who eventually spoke to Claire and convinced her that Olivier regretted his actions. He arranged a reunion for them.\n\nIt was a hard moment for Olivier. He met his son, Alexis, the child he wanted aborted, and the reality of his decision hit him hard. He had been selfish, pushing his girlfriend to do something because it inconvenienced him. More so, Claire was about to get married and Alexis was already calling someone else \'daddy\'. Everything he had done, putting his loved ones through hell, shoved him into a wild depression that almost cost him his rank. Chaplain Bertrand helped Olivier through his crisis and with it, he returned to the Catholic Church. \n\n\ Olivier swore he would do everything possible to rectify the pain he had caused,so he worked harder, and sought more challenges. He qualified to join the Grouped\'intervention de Ia Gendarmerie nationale (GIGN) as their new biohazard expert using drones to maintain and hold quarantine perimeters. He focused on his duty ,on making things right, no matter how much it hurt him in the process. His feelings were irrelevant what mattered was strict observation of his duty. During a Yellow Fever outbreak in Sudan, while protecting a field investigation team, his loud voice scared a frightened mob back and he gained the nickname "Lion" from the locals. \n\nIn 2015, the army asked him to lead the 2nd Dragoons to West Africa to assist medical personnel fighting the Ebola epidemic. Tragedy ensued, and the decisions Olivier made for safety reasons put him at odds with Doc, who blamed him for the death of several medical personnel on-site including Doc's colleague. The tension between the two continues to this day in Team Rainbow. \n\nAfter studying his Jacket, Finka recommended Olivier for Rainbow as a CBRN specialist, and Six agreed. Olivier immediately proved his value when Finka and he uncovered the source of the mysterious mist that came ashore in Sussex and poisoned people, though he claims he shares that success with Twitch, who provided him with the new aerial drone to locate the mist plume. \n\nOlivier has managed to stay in his son's life, but it is an awkward relationship. Alexis does not know how to call him father and Olivier is not sure what it means to be a dad in the day-to-day. He has mended bridges with his parents and sister, his return to the Catholic faith healing those wounds, and while his decision to be a soldier bothers them, he is no longer the thoughtless rebel. He is not a soldier to make life easy on his soul. He bears the weight of responsibility for, what he has done even though Bertrand constantly reminds him that
forgiveness is in the heart of God.</string>
    <string name="lion_profile">Lion is a by-the-books Operator because he doesn\'t trust his civilian instincts. Rules give him structure and allow him to control what he considers the pettier parts of his personality. They give him a safety net when conscience or arrogance could otherwise weaken his resolve and hurt more lives. He bears the weight of responsibility for what he has done and pushes himself to the limits as a form of corporeal punishment. Unfortunately, he is arrogant and has rubbed some people within GIGN and Rainbow the wrong way. Doc thinks he lacks the empathy necessary to help in medical crises while Lion thinks Doc\'s humanitarianism is a liability. Twitch is not happy about being caught in the middle of that fight. His closest friend in GIGN is Montagne, but when Thatcher punched him after he said the wrong thing during a training exercise, Lion almost brought the GIGN
and SAS to blows.
</string>
    <string name="lion_training">Armee and Terre (French Land Army)\n\nSecond-Level In-Combat Medical Training\n\n2nd Dragoon Regiment, GIGN</string>
    <string name="lion_experience">West Africa Ebola Outbreak, Sussex Incident, Lassa Fever Outbreak</string>
    <string name="lion_notes">Olivier spends most of his social time at Church volunteering when he can, or at his apartment reading and staying out of trouble while listening to the angry albums of his teenage years.</string>
    <string name="lion_gadget_name">EE-ONE-D</string>
    <string name="lion_gadget_name_byline">Sonar Detector</string>
    <string name="lion_gadget">The EE-ONE-D detects enemy movement, providing and overview of battlefield.</string>
    <string name="lion_gadget_one">Twitch provided him with an aerial drone while he served with GIGN. The EE-ONE-D helps Lion maintain quarantine by detecting movement in an area, giving an overview of hot zones or of the battlefield. His drone can stay airborne indefinitely, but he must choose the right moment to perform his scans.</string>


    <!-- FINKA -->

    <string name="finka_name">Lera Melnikova</string>
    <string name="finka_dob">June 7th, 1989</string>
    <string name="finka_weight">1.71 M</string>
    <string name="finka_height">68 KG</string>
    <string name="finka_background">Lera was nine when she was diagnosed with a neuropathy that included the slow degeneration of muscles and the loss of sensation in the limbs and extremities.Born three years after the Chernobyl disaster in the irradiated city Gomel, Belarus, she grew up around children already suffering from birth defects. Her diagnosis was the realization of her fears, so when her parents encouraged her and her younger siblings to be physically active, she pushed herself even harder, determined to keep her body in peak condition to weather the neuropathy. She could not be sick if she stayed healthy, her young mind reasoned. \n\nAll three Melnikova children grew up playing sports, with Lera excelling at those requiring agility and finesse but there was always the knowledge that the neuropathy would worsen unless someone found a more permanent solution. She decided that someone was herself.\n\nLera moved to Novosibirsky State University and graduated with a PhD. in Microbiology and Immunology. She remained at NSU in the Biotechnology and Virology Laboratory, her research uncovering treatments for a variety of pathogens and neuropathies including her own through drugs and self-dissolving nanites. While she hadn\'t found a cure, she had found remission.\n\nLera might have stayed in Academia had she not received a visit from the Federal Security Service of the Russian Federation (FSB).. Russian Spetsnaz  operators and special agents faced the ever-growing danger of exposure to hazardous materials including organophosphorus agents like VX gas. For the first me in her life, Lera began thinking outside of her own concerns. Her research ad saved the lives of perfect strangers, and now they were reaching out to her, sending grateful postcards and photos and letters. She could have a greater impact still. Lera jumped at the chance to work with Spetsnaz volunteers in a variety of conditions as she adapted the nanobots to their high-performance physiologies. Quickly, she came to enjoy the sense of competition, camaraderie, and the mental toughness of the Russian Special Forces members. She joined the Army with an eye on becoming a Red Beret herself, on the front lines of saving lives as a Chemical Biological Radiological Nuclear (CBRN) specialist.  \n\n Serving in the Russian Army, Lera rapidly proved herself physically and mentally tough enough to try out for the Spetsnaz. It was a brutal course, culminating in Close quarter Battle (CQB) knife training with Kapkan. A misstep and a flourish from Kapkan, however, opened her face from brow to cheek, but Lera went for a series of bone breaking punches to his nose and ribs before the pain overwhelmed her. They spent the night in the med tent, neither of them speaking, but enjoying a new, unspoken respect between them. From that day forward, she'd earned her moniker, Finka or \"Knife\". Lera became the Spetsnz CBRN Specialist, joining the Vympel UNit under the FSB and using her nanobots to help her unit survice hot zones; she was one of the only people capable of tailoring the nanobots to specific operators.\n\nHer work in restructuring Russian battlefield protocols in the handling and neutralization of dangerous payloads earned her notice, and she became the go-to expert when it came to joint exercises with the other CTUs. Six invited Lera to help Rainbow Six put together a CRBN unit of their own with Olivier \"Lion\" Flament as her first pick.</string>
    <string name="finka_profile">Lera discovered that her neuropathy was slowly growing resistant to treatment. The old fears returned, every ache and pain analysed and scrutinized as she
pushed herself even harder to peak performance.\n\nShe constantly tweaks and modifies her formula to stave off twinges and numbness that she imagines might be the onset of decline. She pushes herself to the point of throwing up after workouts with Iq and Valkyrie, though only Valkyrie understood that punishing limit of physical fitness. Lera is unable to distinguish between the disease and normal fatigue and is driven by he? fears and made excellent by them in the same maddening moment. She is not young anymore, though, but more desperate than ever to hold on to her life. She is trying to find anew treatment while keeping it a secret, but Doc knows and is closely monitoring her condition in case it begins to affect her performance. She has not shared this with anyone else, not Kapkan who is her no-nonsense mentor, and not Tachanka with whom she drinks and flirts.</string>
    <string name="finka_training">Russian Army\n\nSpetsnaz CBRN Specialist , Vympel Unit</string>
    <string name="finka_experience">Sussex Incident, Libyan Decon Project, Lassa Fever Outbreak, Zika Virus Infection.</string>
    <string name="finka_notes">Lera has also recently taken to creating a wall of letters and photos in her workspace, a reminder that her treatments are more than just about helping herself. But she\'s still afraid that the neuropathy might get ahead of her.</string>
    <string name="finka_gadget_name">NANOBOT SHOT</string>
    <string name="finka_gadget_name_byline">Short Physical Enhancement</string>
    <string name="finka_gadget">The nanobots give the team a brief gain in HP and  revives  allies in Down But Not Out State.</string>
    <string name="finka_gadget_one">Finka\'s Adrenal Surge activates pre-injected nanobots made of zinc in operators, releasing a pharmacological cocktail into their system where the zinc is absorbed as a nutrient. These nanites give her team a short boost in HP, they help allies out of DBNO, and they steady the team’s aim. She’s the only one capable of tailoring the nanites to specific operators.</string>

    <!-- UNITS DATA -->


    <string name="sas">The Special Air Service (SAS) is a special forces unit of the British Army. The SAS was founded in 1941 as a regiment, and later reconstituted as a corps in 1950.The unit undertakes a number of roles including covert reconnaissance, counter-terrorism, direct action and hostage rescue. Much of the information and actions regarding the SAS is highly classified, and is not commented on by the British government or the Ministry of Defense due to the sensitivity of their operations.\n\nThe corps currently consists of the 22nd Special Air Service Regiment, the regular component under operational command of United Kingdom Special Forces, as well as the 21st (Artists) Special Air Service Regiment (Reserve) and the 23rd Special Air Service Regiment (Reserve), which are reserve units under operational command of the 1st Intelligence, Surveillance and Reconnaissance Brigade.\n\nThe Special Air Service traces its origins to 1941 and the Second World War. It was reformed as part of the Territorial Army in 1947, named the 21st Special Air Service Regiment (Artists Rifles). The 22nd Special Air Service Regiment, which is part of the regular army, gained fame and recognition worldwide after its televised rescue of all but one of the hostages held during the 1980 Iranian Embassy siege.</string>
    <string name="fbi">FBI Special Weapons and Tactics Teams are specialized tactical teams (SWAT) of the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI). SWAT agents are specially trained to intervene in high-risk events like hostage and barricade situations.The FBI maintains SWAT teams at each of its 56 field offices throughout the country varying in size up to about 42 members.In the event of a large scale problem that local law enforcement does not have the resources to handle, FBI SWAT teams from the local field office, as well as outside the local region can be dispatched to aid the local authorities.\n\nTheir field of action are High risk arrests and assaults (armed and dangerous subjects), Hostage rescue ,Car stops, Counter-terrorism, Maritime Operations, Tubular assaults (aircraft, trains, buses, etc.), Stronghold assaults (structures requiring specialized breaching equipment that local law enforcement might not have access to), Fugitive tracking (in rural environments) , Operations in WMD environments, Dignitary protection, Coordinate multi-location warrant service, Site surveys for high visibility events, Aircraft Hijackings, Specialized sniper operations.</string>
    <string name="gign">GIGN (Groupe d\'intervention de la Gendarmerie nationale)is the elite Police tactical unit of the French National Gendarmerie.Its missions include counter-terrorism, hostage rescue, surveillance of national threats, protection of government officials, and targeting organized crime. \n\nGIGN was established in 1974 following the Munich massacre. Created initially as a relatively small tactical unit specialized in sensitive hostage situations, it has since grown into a larger and more diversified force of nearly 400 members, with expanded responsibilities. GIGN shares jurisdiction of French territory with the National Police special-response units. \n\nGIGN is headquartered in Versailles-Satory near Paris. Although most of its operations take place in France, the unit, as a component of the French Armed Forces, can operate anywhere in the world. Many of its missions are secret, and members are not allowed to be publicly photographed. Since its formation, GIGN has been involved in over 1,800 missions and rescued more than 600 hostages, making it one of the most experienced counter-terrorism units in the world.</string>
    <string name="spetznaz">Spetsnaz is an umbrella term for special forces in Russian and is used in numerous post-Soviet states.\n\nHistorically, the term referred to special military units controlled by the military intelligence service GRU (Spetsnaz GRU). It also describes special purpose units, or task forces of other ministries (such as the Ministry of Internal Affairs ODON and Ministry of Emergency Situations\' special rescue unit) in post-Soviet countries.\n\nAs Spetsnaz is a Russian term, it is typically associated with the special forces units of Russia, but other post-Soviet states often refer to their special forces by the term as well since they inherited their special purpose units from the now-defunct Soviet security agencies. The 5th Spetsnaz Brigade of Belarus or the Alpha Group of the Security Service of Ukraine are both such examples of non-Russian Spetsnaz forces.\n\nIn post-Soviet Russia "Spetsnaz" became a colloquial term as special operations (spetsoperatsiya), from police raids to military operations in internal conflicts, grew more common. Coverage of these operations, and the celebrity status of special operations forces in state-controlled media, encouraged the public to identify many of these forces by name: SOBR, Alpha, Vityaz. The term Spetsnaz has also continued to be used in several other post-Soviet states such as Belarus, Ukraine and Kazakhstan for their own special operations forces. </string>
    <string name="gsg9">Grenzschutzgruppe 9 is the elite Police Tactical Unit of the German Federal Police.\n\nGSG 9 is deployed in cases of hostage-taking, kidnapping, terrorism and extortion. The group may also be used to secure locations, neutralize targets, track down fugitives, and sometimes conduct sniper operations. The unit is very active in developing and testing methods and tactics for these missions. The group may provide advice to the different states of Germany, ministries or international allies. The group assists the Bundespolizei and other federal and local agencies on request.</string>
    <string name="jtf2">Joint Task Force 2 (JTF2)is an elite special operations force of the Canadian Armed Forces.JTF2 serves alongside the Canadian Special Operations Regiment, the Canadian Joint Incident Response Unit and 427 Special Operations Aviation Squadron as part of the Canadian Special Operations Forces Command. The unit is currently based at Dwyer Hill, near Ottawa, Ontario, and plans to move to a new facility to be built at CFB Trenton by 2019.\n\nServing as the centerpiece of Canada\'s special operations, JTF2 is primarily tasked with counter-terrorism operations but also specializes in direct action, hostage rescue, personnel recovery, and foreign internal defense. Much of the information regarding Joint Task Force 2 is classified, and is not commented on by the Government of Canada.</string>
    <string name="navy">The United States Navy\'s Sea, Air and Land Teams, commonly abbreviated as the Navy SEALs, are the U.S. Navy\'s primary special operations force and a component of the Naval Special Warfare Command. Among the SEALs main functions are conducting small-unit maritime military operations that originate from, and return to, a river, ocean, swamp, delta, or coastline.The SEALs are trained to operate in all environments (sea, air, and land) for which they are named.\n\nAs of August 2017, all active SEALs are currently male and members of the U.S. Navy.The CIA\'s highly secretive and elite Special Operations Group (SOG) recruits operators from SEAL Teams,with joint operations going back to the MACV-SOG during the Vietnam War.This cooperation still exists today, as evidenced by military operations in Iraq and Afghanistan.</string>
    <string name="bope">Batalhão de Operações Policiais Especiais (BOPE) is a special police unit of the Military Police of Rio de Janeiro State (PMERJ) in Brazil. Due to the nature of crime in favelas, BOPE units have extensive experience in urban warfare as well as progression in confined and restricted environments. It also utilizes equipment deemed more powerful than traditional civilian law enforcement.\n\nBOPE of PMERJ is one of the best known units of its kind among Brazil's military police organizations. Military Police of Alagoas and Santa Catarina states also call their tactical units BOPE, while the military police of the Federal District, Piauí, and Rio Grande do Sul states call their forces "Special Operations Battalion(s)" ("Batalhão de Operações Especiais" or "BOE").</string>
    <string name="sat">The Special Assault Teams are Police Tactical Units of the Japanese police. They are established in some Prefectural Polices supervised by the National Police Agency. The SAT is mandated, along with the Anti-Firearms Squad and the Counter-NBC Terrorism Squad, for counter terrorism missions and incidents involving firearms or criminals which require an armed response beyond the capabilities of local law enforcement in Japan. Most information on the unit has been confidential, its existence officially revealed only in 1996.\n\nCurrently, SAT is officially known in Japanese as Special Unit and individual teams officially take the name of the Metropolitan or Prefectural police departments to which they are assigned; an example would be Tokyo Metropolitan Police Department Special Unit.</string>
    <string name="geo">The Grupo Especial de Operaciones is the Police Tactical Unit of the Spanish Cuerpo Nacional de Policía (English: National Police Corps). The GEO has response capabilities and is responsible for VIP protection duties, as well as countering and responding to terrorism. Organized along the lines of many other Police Tactical Units throughout Europe, the GEO is focused on dealing with terrorist attacks, including aircraft hijackings as well as maritime threats and hostage taking. \n\nThe GEO can also be used in a support role for Spanish Police operations outside the realm of terrorism, and is active in protecting visiting heads of state and providing security for high-profile events such as the 1992 Summer Olympics held in Barcelona.The GEO is in the ATLAS Network, that includes all the national police tactical units of European Union countries, and other countries excluded from the European Union.</string>
    <string name="sdu">The Special Duties Unit (SDU) is the elite tactical unit of the Hong Kong Police Force tasked with countering terrorist attacks, hostage rescue and tackling serious crime involving firearms.[2] The SDU is a subdivision of the riot control Police Tactical Unit which is part of \'A\' Department (Operations and Support).\n\nThe SDU is based at the Police Tactical Unit Headquarters in Fanling.The SDU also undertakes underwater search and recovery for search and rescue operations and to recover evidence.The SDU was established in 1974 by the British Hong Kong Government in response to the ever-increasing threat of international terrorism.The SDU, consisting of ten odd members, used existing police weaponry and devised their own tactics.</string>
    <string name="grom">JW GROM is Poland\'s elite counter-terrorism unit. The unit\'s other name is Jednostka Wojskowa 2305 (Military Unit 2305). GROM was originally modelled on NATO\'s tier one (special mission units) special operations units such as the US Army\'s Delta Force, the US Navy\'s SEAL Team Six (DEVGRU) and the British Army\'s SAS.\n\nGROM, which stands for Grupa Reagowania Operacyjno-Manewrowego which also means "thunder", is one of the five special operation forces units of the Polish Armed Forces. It was officially activated on July 13, 1990. It is deployed in a variety of special operations and unconventional warfare roles, including anti-terrorist operations and projection of force behind enemy lines</string>
    <string name="x707thsmb">The 707th Special Mission Battalion is a special forces unit in the Republic of Korea Army Special Warfare Command.The unit was formed after the Munich massacre, which forced the South Korean government to create a counter-terrorist unit in time for the 1988 Olympics that would be held on South Korean soil.The unit has about 200 men and women organized in two assault companies, one support company, and one all-female company that could be used as bodyguards or for low-visibility operations.\n\nThe 707th SMB has also been called on by the South Korean government to prioritize potential counter-terrorist operations against any possible threats on South Korean soil. The unit is South Korea’s primary counter-terrorist and quick reaction force. The unit\’s soldiers – once distinguished by their black berets (before the standardization of the black beret for all active soldiers) – are tasked with conducting urban counter terrorist missions, and constitute the Army\’s quick-reaction force for emergencies.The battalion\'s nickname is 'White Tiger.'</string>


    <!-- OPERATOR TIPS -->

    <string name="sledge_tip">Sledgehammer can destroy unreinforced walls, unreinforced hatches , destructible floors and barricades.
	\n\nSledgehammer can create new lines of sight by using it to create holes in walls or floors.
	\n\nSledgehammer can be used to create new entry and rotation holes for Attackers.
	\n\nSledgehammer can destroy Barbed wire ,Castle Armors and most Defender gadgets with one hit.
	\n\nThe usage of Sledgehammer on anything will reduce its durability.
	\n\nThe Sledgehammer contains 25 charges to break stuff.
	\n\nDestroying a wall will Sledgehammer takes two charges while all others take one charge. Swinging the hammer without any contact does not count as a charge.
	\n\nThere is a slight delay when trying to unequip the Sledgehammer, during which Sledge is vulnerable to gunfire and cannot defend himself.
	\n\nSledgehammer is also capable of killing enemies with one hit. It counts as two charges.
	\n\nWhen being close to the wall while hitting it with the hammer,it will destroy the double layer of the wall completely. When used a bit away from the wall,  it only destroys one layer of the wall leaving the second layer intact.\n\n</string>

    <string name="thatcher_tip">Thatcher has EMP grenades that will destroy or deactivate the Defender gadgets.
	\n\nEMP will destroy Smoke Gas Grenades , Mute Signal Disruptor, Kapkan Entry Denial Devices, Jager Active Defense Systems, Bandit Shock Wire, Valkyrie Black Eyes, Lesion Gu Mines, Ela Grizmot Mines, Nitro Cells ,Defender Cameras and more.
	\n\nEMP will deactivate Vigil ERC-7, Pulse Heartbeat Sensor and Echo Yokai Drone for while if caught in the radius.
	\n\nEMP will disable all Defender Weapon sights for 10 seconds if in the affected radius. ACOGs will also be disabled but only when Defenders are not aiming down the sights.
	\n\nEMP will not affect any Attacker gadgets.
	\n\nEMP will disable the lights in the room it was thrown into for a while.
	\n\nEMP will disable Laser sights of Defenders which reduce their hip fire accuracy.
	\n\nEMP will pass through walls and surfaces, You can destroy gadgets on other side of the wall or floor if they are in the radius of the blast.
	\n\nEMP grenades cannot be cooked and will activate seconds after being thrown.
	\n\nWhen you hear the buzzing sound of a Mute Jammer,  throwing an EMP at your feet will destroy the Mute Jammer in proximity.
	\n\nEMP will make a loud noise when activated, Use that to mask the sound from your footsteps.
	\n\nAfter throwing an EMP in a room, Do not try to push aggressively inside because EMP will disable the lights in the room and will make it  harder to you to spot the Defenders. Also note that it will also be difficult for the Defenders to spot you in dark.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ash_tip">Ash can fire CREM breaching charges from long distances to safely destroy surfaces from behind cover.
	\n\nAsh CREM breaches are not remotely activated, so they detonate on impact even if there is a Mute Jammer around.
	\n\nAsh CREM deals a mere 85 damage to 1 Armor Operator.\n\nAsh CREM breach on contact with defender will deal 50 damage irrespective of the Armor of Defender.
	\n\nWhen walls are not completely covered by reinforcements, CREM can make new line around them.
	\n\nAsh CREM breach can remove Mira Black Mirror if it is deployed on unreinforced walls.
	\n\nAsh CREM breaches can open up floors with high range of explosion radius.
	\n\nAsh CREM can be used to destroy very hard to reach places like higher windows or ceilings.
	\n\nAsh CREM can be used to clear Barbed wires and Shield in the way of the Attackers.
	\n\nAsh CREM can be used to destroy Castle barricades.\n\nAsh CREM can be used to open unreinforced hatches and walls.
	\n\nAsh CREM breach will destroy Defender gadgets if they are in radius of the explosion.\n\n</string>

    <string name="thermite_tip">Thermite Exothermic Charge can destroy reinforced walls and hatches.
	\n\nUsing Exothermic Charges on unreinforced walls is waste of utility.
	\n\nDetonation of an Exothermic Charge takes 3 seconds.
	\n\nExplosion radius from Exothermic Charge is large compared to other methods.
	\n\nDetonating an Exothermic Charge in the junction of the wall and floor will destroy them both partially. If there is a hatch near the junction, it will be destroyed along with the wall.
	\n\nDetonating Exothermic Charge will destroy areas adjacent to it. This can be used to bypass certain Mute Signal Disruptor and destroy hatches and walls even if they are jammed.
	\n\nThermite can encounter Bandit trick by using Advanced Gadget Deployment model in game options. Switch areas and confuse Bandit as to where you are placing your Exothermic Charges.
	\n\nWhen placing Exothermic Charges, be sure to get hit from battery shock and place the Exothermic charge as soon as Thatcher EMP goes off. This will help you counter Bandit trick.\n\n</string>

    <string name="twitch_tip">Twitch has her Twitch Drones as her primary Drone. One Drone is activated during preparation phase.
	\n\nTwitch Drones can shock enemies and reduce 10 hp.\n\nTwitch Drones can destroy defender gadgets and cameras.
	\n\nTwitch drones have a limit in how higher their shots can reach.
	\n\nBoth Twitch Drones have 5 darts each.
	\n\nTwitch drones can destroy Mira Black Mirrors.\n\nVigil Video Disruptor will turn off temporarily if shot by a Twitch Drone.
	\n\nTwitch Drones cannot jump. They can only travel on ground.
	\n\nTwitch Drones are quieter and smoother that other drones.
	\n\nFrost Welcome Mat cannot be damaged by Twitch Drones.
	\n\nTwitch Drones can be used to kill downed Defenders.\n\n</string>

    <string name="montagne_tip">The Extended Shield protects the entire front body from Defenders.
	\n\nThe Extended Shield also protects his sides to an extent.
	\n\nHis Smokes can be used to cut off multiple line of sights while pushing a single direction.
	\n\nHis Smokes can help in a Smoked Defuser Plant.
	\n\nNitro Cells will deal him little damage.
	\n\nThe Ballistic Shield will be knocked left when melee attacked by Defender. In such situation he should turn right to adjust with the knocked shield to get cover from it.
	\n\nThe Extendable Shield can be used to block doorways when fully extended thereby denying passage for Defenders.
	\n\nMontagne can use laser with his handgun to perform hip-fire shots which can be quite deadly if aimed perfect.
	\n\nMontagne is well suited to perform a quick recon and provide information to other Attackers.
	\n\nMontagne deals less damage from Kapkan traps if his Shield is extended.
	\n\nMontagne when crouch walks with shield is less vulnerable to bullets than walking with no extended shield.\n\n</string>

    <string name="glaz_tip">Glaz uses his sniper to support Attackers from long distance.
	\n\nGlaz sniper can see Defenders through smoke with the help of his Thermal sights.
	\n\nGlaz can destroy Castle Armor Panel by shooting at them 12 times.
	\n\nGlaz can open unreinforced hatches by shooting 3 times with his sniper.
	\n\nGlaz sniper can penetrate two surfaces at once.
	\n\nGlaz can use smoke grenades from other Attackers to help him with his thermal sight.
	\n\nGlaz can penetrate the windows in Plane maps.
	\n\nGlaz is very helpful in protecting defuser after plant as he can cover for it from a very long distance.
	\n\nGlaz can provide covers for Attackers from Defender run outs from a long distance.\n\n</string>

    <string name="fuze_tip">Fuze is a very destructive operator. He is often known for his disregard for civilian life.
	\n\nFuze Cluster charges are effective in clearing out rooms without engaging in close range combat.
	\n\nFuze Cluster charges injects small explosive pellets through the surface in which it is being deployed, be it floor or wall.
	\n\nThe charge pellets are deployed in other side of the wall or floor upon detonation.
	\n\Cluster Frag Grenades are deployed in count of 5 from right to left. They detonate in the order they are deployed.
	\n\nEach pellet have a range of 42m and deal lethal damage.
	\n\nCluster Charge pellets can bounce back surfaces too, Be wary how you place them.
	\n\nFuze Charges can pierce through Castle Armored Panels and create a hole when doing so. This hole can be used for line of sight into the room.
	\n\nFuze can be combined with Lion to lock Defenders into a room and fuzing them to kill them all or injure them.
    \n\nFuze Cluster Charges can be used tactically to create confusion and chaos among Defenders.
	\n\nInstead of using Fuze Cluster Charges random to get kills, placing them in conventional spots based on map knowledge will yield you confirmed kills.\n\n</string>

    <string name="blitz_tip">Blitz Shield can blind enemies when flashed.
	\n\nDefenders are very vulnerable when in line of sight of the flash as they are blinded completely.
	\n\nBlitz has total of 4 flashes.
	\n\nBlitz can still use the Flash when aiming down the sights.
	\n\nBlitz is effective for targeting roamers and get rid of them early.
	\n\nDealing a Blitz alone is very difficult for any Defender.
	\n\nBlitz can run with his shield up and flash at the same time making him very hard to deal with.
	\n\nBlitz flash will cause full temporary blindness at range of 4m and works partially till 5m.\n\n</string>

    <string name="iq_tip">Iq can detect Defender gadgets and destroy them through floors and walls.
	\n\nIq can detect bombs and Defender gadgets from a distance.
	\n\nIq is very effective in hunting Pulse as his Gadget will be detected by Iq Spectre.
	\n\nIq is very effective in hunting Vigil as his Gadget will be detected by Iq Spectre.
	\n\nIq can find Kapkan Entry Denial Devices, Nitro cells, Jager Active Defense Systems, Bandit Shock Wires, Smoke Gas Canisters, Valkyries Black Eyes, Echo Yokai Drone, Ela Grizmot Mines and more.
	\n\nIq is very effective in preventing Defenders from using Valkyrie Black Eyes for run out kills.
	\n\nIq is very effective in identifying Lesion GU mines which are invisible to naked eye.
	\n\nIq can detect phones when Defenders are using them to check their cameras.
    \n\nIq is very effective in finding Echo Yokai drone and destorying it. She can detect it through walls and can destroy it.
	\n\nIq can detect phones when Defenders are using them to prevent call from Dokkaebi.\n\n</string>

    <string name="buck_tip">Buck uses a Shotgun attached to his primary to destroy surfaces very fast.
	\n\nBuck can destroy surfaces very quickly be it floors, walls or hatches. They must not be reinforced.
	\n\nBuck can create new lines of sight from above, from below and to adjacent rooms.
	\n\nBuck can create holes that can be used for vaulting into.
	\n\nThe Skeleton Key contains 16 shells in reserve.
	\n\nBuck is very useful in all map but you must have good map knowledge to use him to his full potential.
	\n\nBuck can create chaos by destroying floors and driving Defenders below the floor into sense of fear.\n\n</string>

    <string name="blackbeard_tip">Blackbeard uses a Rifle Mounted Shield to protect him from bullet fire.
	\n\nThe Rifle Shield protect shots to his. head This give him a great advantage to be aggressive when peeking.
	\n\nBlackbeard has two rifle shields to deploy.
	\n\nBlackbeard can switch between the two anytime if its not broken.
	\n\nRifle shields withstand upto 60 hp.
	\n\nWhen Rifle Shield is equipped, he moves very slow.
	\n\nBlackbeard can recover his normal speed by switching from Rifle Shield Primary to Secondary handgun D50.
	\n\nBlackbeard DMR is very deadly if used on a precise level.
	\n\nBlackbeard is very effective in holding flanks.
	\n\nBlackbeard is very effective in rappelling, He can peek windows and doors with the help of his shield protecting his head from bullet fire.
	\n\nBlackbeard is very effective in holding angles from windows or doors of buildings.\n\n</string>

    <string name="capitao_tip">Capitao Tactical Crossbow has two different bolts: Asphyxiating Bolts and Micro Smoke Grenades. You can switch either at any time.
	\n\nAsphyxiating Bolts can be used to block passage of doors and windows.\n\nAsphyxiating Bolts can be used to kill downed Defenders.
	\n\nAsphyxiating Bolts can be used to kill Bandit if he is trying to active Bandit trick.
	\n\nThe radius of Asphyxiating Bolts are very small. If any Defender tried to pass it, they will die.
	\n\nAsphyxiating Bolts can be used to trap and kill Defenders camped in a corner.
	\n\n Defenders behind the cover of a shield can be killed easily by using it.
	\n\nA direct impact of the bolt deals 5 damage.
	\n\nWhen arrows are shot to the head of Defenders, It will do normal damage and not instant kill them.
	\n\nCapitao bolts will not be destroyed by Jager ADS.
	\n\nUnlike normal smoke, Capitao Micro smoke grenades release smoke which are blue in color.\n\n</string>

    <string name="hibana_tip">X-KAIROS pellets are useful in opening reinforced walls and hatches.
	\n\nX-KAIROS will help you open three reinforced hatches at most.
	\n\nX-KAIROS need to be detonated after impact manually.
	\n\nX-KAIROS can also be used to create entry passages in walls.
	\n\nX-KAIROS can be used to open up floor down to create new lines of sight.
	\n\nA single pellet from X-KAIROS can destroy open a hatch.
	\n\nX-KAIROS will shoot 6 pellets at a time.
	\n\nX-KAIROS pellets detonated once will create a hole that helps you crawl into walls.
	\n\nX-KAIROS pellets detonated twice will create a hole that helps you crouch walk into walls.
	\n\nX-KAIROS pellets detonated thrice will create a hole that helps you walk or sprint into walls.
	\n\nX-KAIROS can also be used to burn out Jager Active Defense System. When X-KAIROS is shot, each pellet will be destroyed by ADS seperately.
	\n\nX-KAIROS help you open Mira Black Mirrors.
	\n\nX-KAIROS takes 5 secs to detonate while Thermite Exothermic Charge only takes 3 secs.
	\n\nX-KAIROS can be aimed to precisely fire pellets to a surface.
	\n\nX-KAIROS When used at junction of walls and floors, It opens both the wall and floor partially.
	\n\nX-KAIROS can be used to destroy Castle barricades</string>

    <string name="jackal_tip">Jackal is very effective in hunting roamers by tracking their footprints.
	\n\nJackal Eyenox can see footprints of Defenders and scan them to locate their position. The Eyenox pings the location of the Defender 5 times in 20 seconds.
	\n\nDefender footprints are colored based on the time it was made, red mean 0 sec ago, yellow means 20s ago, green means 45s ago, blue means 65s ago and the tracks disappears at 90s mark.
	\n\nFootprint tracks will not be made by the Defenders if they are prone.
	\n\nAll Attackers will see the live ping update of Defender who is being tracked by Jackal.
	\n\nJackal is very effective in detecting any movement of Defenders in the vicinity.
	\n\nJackal shotgun can be used to make rotation holes quickly.
	\n\nJackal is very effective to find the position of last Defender alive.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ying_tip">Ying Candela works like Stun grenades.They blind the Defenders and leaves them vulnerable.
	\n\nCandelas can be placed on breakable surfaces to fire flashes onto the other side.
	\n\nCandelas are very effective in getting the Defuser Planted by blinding Defenders.
	\n\nCandelas can be used to waste Jager Active Defense System by placing them on barricades to  fire flashes in line of sight of those ADS.
	\n\nCandelas can be cooked before release, Doing so delays the detonation and rolls them on the ground for a while. The rolling time depends on how long you wait to release them initially.
	\n\nCandelas can be punched through Castle Armor too.
	\n\nYing wears special goggles that allows her to see through the flashes.
	\n\nYing is very effective in flashing any Defender behind a Black Mirror and prevent them from firing.
	\n\Ying will also blind Attackers if not communicated well.\n\n</string>

    <string name="zofia_tip">Zofia can fire Impact Grenades and Proximity Concussion Grenades. She can switch them both any time.
	\n\nZofia has 2 Impact Grenades and 4 Concussion Grenades.
	\n\nConcussion Grenades cause Visual and Mobility disorientation effects.
	\n\nConcussion Grenades when hit on a surface will rebound and detonate.
	\n\nConcussion Grenades will detonate when they come in proximity of a Defender.
	\n\nZofia is resistant to Ela proximity mine and can recover in half the time taken by other Attackers.
	\n\nZofia has a ability to withstand when in down state. She will recover herself up 5 percent of baseline health. It taked 5 seconds to stand up from downed state.
	\n\nThere is a arc present to the grenade trajectory of the mines.
	\n\nThere is no reload process for the grenades. Zofia can fire the grenades one after another.
	\n\nZofia impact grenades can be used to destroy Castle barricades.
	\n\nZofia impact grenades can be used to destroy Shields and Barbed wire in the path of Attackers.
	\n\nZofia can be used to destroy Mira Black mirror if it is placed in unreinforced walls.
	\n\nZofia impact grenade will destroy Defender gadgets if they are in radius of the explosion.\n\n</string>

    <string name="dokkaebi_tip">The Logic Bomb hacks Defender system and calls them. It makes Defenders phones vibrate and give out a buzzing sound helping Attackers locate them easily.
	\n\nWhen Defender phones are called, they will have no longer be able to access Defender cameras unless they switch off the phone.
	\n\nLogic Bomb call can only be made twice Use them wisely.
	\n\nLogic Bomb can hack the phone dropped by any Defender who is killed. This hacks the Defender camera network including Valkyrie Black Eyes and makes the camera feed available to the Attackers.
	\n\nLogic Bomb calls are very helpful to locate Roamers.
	\n\nHacked cameras are accessible to both Attackers and Defenders.
	\n\nExplosives will not destroy phones of Defenders, they must be destroyed manually.
	\n\nDokkaebi calls can be used to quickly find the roamer who is close by.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lion_tip">Lion EE-One-D drone will detect Defender movement and provide their real time outline for the 4 second duration when its active.
	\n\nLion scan revealing enemy position of Defender can be seen by all the Attackers.
	\n\nLion can call two scans per round.
	\n\nLion can use his Drone with interval of 20 seconds.
	\n\nLion ability is perfect to kill any moving Defender from above or below the floor.
	\n\nLion is a good counter to prevent Defenders from prefiring from Mira Black Mirror.
	\n\nLion is also very useful to detect any Defenders who is trying to spawn peek .\n\n</string>

    <string name="finka_tip">Finka Adrenal shot provide set of abilities which increases the performance of Attackers.
	\n\nFinka shot will last for 20 seconds.
	\n\nFinka has three Adrenal surge shots.
	\n\nFinka Adrenal shot also provide a health boost of 20hp.
	\n\nFinka can use her ability Adrenal shot to revive team mates when down.
	\n\nFinka Adrenal shot will reduce the recoil of Attacker weapons to a huge amount in that duration.
	\n\nFinka is very useful when played aggressive, or when a team rushes into the site aggressively.
	\n\nWhen Finka ability is active, Attackers will move easily through Barbed Wire, recover faster from Stun grenades and Concussion Mines.
	\n\nFinka can prevent Caveira interrogation by reviving the downed Attacker instantly.\n\n</string>

    <string name="smoke_tip">Smoke Gas grenades stick to surfaces and can be detonated remotely.
	\n\nSmoke Gas grenades release toxic content dealing critical damage.
	\n\nSmoke Gas grenades damages 15 health points every second regardless of armor.
	\n\nSmoke Gas grenades can be used to kill downed enemies.
	\n\nSmoke Gas grenades can be detonated on impact like nitro cells.
	\n\nSmoke Gas grenades release toxic gas which is dense and deny vision through it. This can be used for rotation or escaping from Attackers if caught.
	\n\nUsing Smoke Gas grenades when Attackers are walking through Barbed Wire will surely down them and kill them as they take more damage the longer they are in the gas.
	\n\nSmoke gas grenades deal more damage per second to Attackers if Finka nanobot is active on the Attackers.
	\n\nWhen Attackers try to plant defuser with the help of smoke, Smoke can use his gas grenades to deny the plant.
	\n\nSmoke shotgun and impact grenades can be used to create rotation holes between sites.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mute_tip">Mute Jammer are portable devices and has a range of 5m.
	\n\nThey disrupt all Attacker gadget that are used remotely.
	\n\nMute Jammer can disrupt Jackal Eyenox making him blind.
	\n\nMute Jammer can prevent Defenders from being called by Dokkaebi Logic Bomb.
	\n\nMute Jammer can prevent movement of Attacker drones and their recon.
	\n\nWhen Defenders are near Mute Jammer, their phones will not ring if Dokkaebi calls.
	\n\nWhen placed between two reinforced walls, Mute Jammer prevent Thermite and Hibana from destroying the wall as their gadgets cannot be detonated.
	\n\nIn preparation phase if a drone is jammed by Mute jammer and is not destroyed. The Attacker will not be able to see the feed from other Attacker drones.
	\n\nMute Signal Disruptor are placed in doorways to prevent drones from entering the room. Place them in a way Attackers wont shoot them.
	\n\nWhen Defenders are near Mute Jammer when Lion uses his Drone, they will not be detected even if they move.\n\n</string>

    <string name="castle_tip">Castle has 3 Armor Panels which he can barricades in doors and windows. They are bulletproof and are very much tougher than normal barricades.
	\n\nArmor Panel once barricaded, can be pulled down by any defender. They will return back to Castle.
	\n\nCastle helps slowing down Attackers and deny line of sights that are more vulnerable.
	\n\nWhen these panels are combined with Mute, they can prevent Attacker from opening it with Breach Charges.
	\n\nDefenders cannot make hole in Armor Panels except with Vigil shotgun.
	\n\nUsing Thermite and Hibana to open Caste is waste of utility.
	\n\nArmor Panel when pre-hit 11 times, can be used to make surprise run-outs by hitting once and using element of surprise on Attackers.
	\n\nImpact Grenades can destroy Armor Panels on impact.
	\n\nWhen Attacker tries to melee attack Panels, Defenders can use nitro cell to kill them,or shoot Attackers in legs exposed under the Panel to prevent them from opening.
	\n\nArmor Panels can be used to deny entry for Attackers into the objective.\n\n</string>

    <string name="pulse_tip">Pulse can detect Attacker in proximity using the Heartbeat Sensor.
	\n\nPulse is very useful to inform Attacker movement to others.
	\n\nPulse can detect and use nitro cells to blow up Attackers from below.
	\n\nPulse can detect Attackers and shoot through surfaces to kill them.
	\n\nPulse is a effective roamer who can detect enemies and outsmart them with creative plays.
	\n\nPulse is very effective in analyzing the Attacker movement and their plan.
	\n\nPulse is useful in detecting the position of Defuser plant when Attackers use smoke and plant.
	\n\nPulse can also prevent defuser from being planted by playing below the floor.
	\n\nPulse is effective in locating Fuze.\n\n</string>

    <string name="doc_tip">Stim Pistol heals Defenders for 40 hp when hit with it.
	\n\nDoc can pick himself up when down using his Stim Pistol.
	\n\nStim Pistol revives a person who is down with 75 hp.
	\n\nWhen used on a downed Defender it gets them up without any help from other Defenders.
	\n\nStim Pistol has pinpoint  hipfire accuracy. It can be shot without aiming down.
	\n\nStim Pistol has ability to overheal Defenders. It is useful when trying to face a group of Attackers or when trying to take back Defuser.
	\n\nThe overheal if done, decays at rate of 1 hp per second until baseline 100 is achieved.
	\n\nDoc has 3 shots in Multiplayer and 5 in Terrorist Hunt mode.
	\n\nInstead of using Stim Pistol to revive downed Defenders, if Doc tries to revive them manually and later provide them a Stim shot he can provide more health points.\n\n</string>

    <string name="rook_tip">Rook Armor Plates come in a Satchel.It has five armors in it.
	\n\nRook Armor reduces 20 percent damage.
	\n\nRook Armor does not affect headshot kills.
	\n\nRook cannot pick up Satchel once dropped.
	\n\nArmor Plates when worn always put you in a downed state instead of being killed But when shot after being downed kills you.
	\n\nOperators wearing Rook Armor can only be downed once per round. Next time, instead of being downed, they will be killed.
	\n\nWhen downed wearing a armor, the bleedout is doubled for 120 secs.
	\n\nOperators will die from melee even when Armor Plates are worn.\n\n</string>

    <string name="kapkan_tip">Kapkan uses Entry Denial Device to damage unwary Attackers.
	\n\nEDD deal a damage of 60hp.
	\n\nThey can be attached to frames of doors and windows.
	\n\nThe laser of EDD cannot be seen.\
	\n\nEDD can be placed in multiple heights on  door frames. It depends on where you look when placing them.
	\n\nWhen placed wisely they can deal great damage to Attackers.
	\n\Deploy EDD and barricade doors and windows. This way any careless Attacker trying to break the barricade will trigger the EDD.
	\n\Deploy EDD and place a shield in doorways. This way any careless Attacker trying to jump over the shield will trigger the EDD.
	\n\nKapkan can help in providing intel for Roamers on Attacker movement. Place EDD in locations where Attackers might push. When those EDD go off, Kapkan will be notified of it. This was he can learn about Attacker presence there.
	\n\nKapkan must be careful not to be detected by drones while placing EDD mines.
	\n\nFind good locations to place the EDD mines where Attackers will not detect them.\n\n</string>

    <string name="tachanka_tip">The LMG gives a high level of protection.
	\n\nWhen used wisely with a Defender Shield in front, it can be used for a great suppressive fire at entrances.
	\n\nTachanka can deploy LMG and pick it up later.
	\n\nWhen unmanned ,LMG can be used by any Defender or even Attacker.
	\n\nThe Mounted LMG has a protective shield on the top that protects head from direct  gunfire.
	\n\nThe LMG Mount has a 60 degrees limitation in any directions.
	\n\nThe LMG has greater destruction power, it can destroy surfaces to create new lines of sights and provide support to Defenders in that area.\n\n</string>

    <string name="jager_tip">Jager is a powerful Defense Operator.
	\n\nJager provide anti grenade support using his Magpies - Active Defense System.
	\n\nADS detects and destroys any projectile coming in its line of sight.
	\n\nJager have 3 Magpies. They are placed right next to windows or doors to prevent Attackers from using remote detonated devices.
	\n\nADS can simultaneously destroy two projectiles.
	\n\nADS can destroy Frag grenades, Stun Grenades, Smoke Grenades, Ash CREM, Thatcher EMPs, Grenades from Fuze Cluster Charge, Hibana XKAIROS, Ying Candela,Zofia Impact and Concussion grenades.\n\n</string>

    <string name="bandit_tip">Bandit can place Shock Wire on all metallic gadgets, Barbed wires, Shields, Reinforced walls.
	\n\nShock can be identified with sparks coming out of metal objects.
	\n\nShock Wires destroy Attacker gadgets when in contact with.
	\n\nBandit shotgun is very effective at close range.
	\n\nBandit can active switch the batteries to prevent Thermite from using his Exothermic Charge by destroying it.
	\n\nBandit can prevent Mira Black Mirrors being open by Hibana XKAIROS by shocking the walls.
	\n\nDefender gadgets can also be destroyed by Bandit Shock Wires.
	\n\nAttacker in contact with shock sparks will deal 10 damage per second. They also cause disorientations.
	\n\nOne Shock Wire can electrify one Barbed Wire or One Shield or One Reinforced wall.
	\n\nIt is possible for Bandit Shock Wire to get kills even after Bandit is dead.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mira_tip">Mira uses Black Mirrors that are deployed on walls that help Defenders create a one way view to the other side.
	\n\nThey can be tactically used to defend a location. When needed the gas canister in Black Mirror can be destroyed creating a murder hole that Defenders can use.
	\n\nBlack Mirrors are useful to hold Bomb Defuser plant. Combine Mira with Smoke and you can deny plant.
	\n\nMira Black Mirrors can be places at head or crouch level.
	\n\nCommon strategy is to reinforce one of two adjacent walls and place a Mira Black Mirror in the reinforced wall, Leaving the other wall soft fire when Attackers are in line of sight to the front.
	\n\nOnce deployed Mira Black Mirrors cannot be removed from walls.
	\n\nUsing shotgun to shoot on sides on Mira Black Mirror create deep angles on the sides to the other side.
	\n\nMira can prevent Attackers from entering the objective with the help of her Black Mirrors.\n\n</string>

    <string name="valkyrie_tip">Valkyrie can throw upto three Black Eye cameras which extend three more camera feed to Defenders.
	\n\nBlack Eyes can be thrown anywhere and they stick to the surface.
	\n\nBlack Eyes create new intel available for Defenders.
	\n\nBlack Eyes are gyroscopic and have 360 degree viewing angle if thrown to appropriate surfaces at correct angles.
	\n\nBlack Eyes transmit color video footage with a blue tint as opposed to black and white footage of Defender cameras .
	\n\nBlack Eyes are denoted by blue dots in Defenders camera UI.
	\n\nBlack Eyes help you plan your runouts on Attackers when they are not expecting.\n\n</string>

    <string name="caveira_tip">Caveira is a powerful stealth operator. She is a powerful Roamer.
        \n\nCaveira can interrogate the Attackers in 5 seconds and kills them after that.
        \n\nCaveira can use Silent step for 10 seconds and need to be recharged before using again.
	\n\nCaveira handgun Luison is a specially modified version that does a 99 hp damage at close range. It is guaranteed to put Attackers in a downed state when used. When shot at Attackers who are downed it will kill them.
	\n\nCaveira Silent Step will enable her to walk, sprint in a stealth approach, making very less noise compared to others.
	\n\nWhen Jackal is tracking Caveira, She can activate her Silent Step ability to prevent pinging of her location.
	\n\nWhen she uses her Silent Step, she will not make footstep tracks.
	\n\nCaveira is best used for flanks and to surprise Attackers who are unwary from behind.
	\n\nCaveira, when she finds an Attacker down, can interrogate them to track the other Attackers in real time. It shows their name and icons for 10 secs.
	\n\nCaveira, when using Silent Step melee, an Attacker will always be put in downed state so that she can interrogate them.
	\n\nCaveira is well known to use her Impact Grenades to rotate around quickly and surprise Attackers in multiple angles</string>

    <string name="echo_tip">Echo uses his remotely controlled Yokai Drone to do recon on Attackers and disorient them with his Sonic blast.
	\n\nEcho can deploy the drone to higher locations while aiming.
	\n\nYokai Drone cannot jump and can be moved vertically up to the ceiling and sticks to it.
	\n\nYokai Drone has a 2 sec jump cooldown and is limited to jump distance of 5 m.
	\n\nYokai drone when in ceiling will render it invisible but a little bit visible when closely seen. Yokai drone will blast an Attacker with sonic bursts which will disorient them and make their movements dizzy. This disorientation is very effective if Attacker tries to run away after being attacked by the drone as it worsens the effect much more .
	\n\nCamera feed from Yokai can only be seen by Echo, Even if Echo is dead, he will be able to access the camera feed from the drone.
	\n\nBlast range is 14m for Echo drone, The blast has no travel time and is instantaneous.
	\n\nYokai blast need to be targeted to the Attackers to cause disorientation effect.
	\n\nYokai drone cannot scan Attackers.
	\n\nYokai drone blast can have interesting effect on Attackers movement, it will cancel action they are performing like planting a Defuser and more.
	\n\nEcho drone can be used to prevent the Attacker from planting the defuser as it cancels their action. This is very useful at end of round as denying Defuser plant will make the Defenders win the round.
	\n\nEcho drone effect will disable the effect of Finka nanobots to Attackers.
	\n\nYokai will lose signal if it goes out of Defenders area, You will have 3 secs before you lose signal. Once Yokai drone loses signal outside, It can only be picked up Echo himself.
	\n\nEcho is immune to Dokkaebi Logic Bomb Call .
	\n\nYokai drone can touch Bandit Shock Wire and not be destroyed by it.
	\n\nBe careful while placing Defender Shield in doors I will prevent Yokai Drone from moving outside the room and vice versa.\n\n</string>

    <string name="frost_tip">Frost uses Welcome Mats, which when in contact with will down the Attackers. Welcome Mats have no effect on Defenders.
	\n\nIf Attacker was already in a downed state and was revived earlier, stepping on a Welcome Mat will kill them instantly.
	\n\nWelcome Mat, when it catches Attackers will make a very distinct sound of "clank" to notify about it to the Defenders.
	\n\nWhen Attackers are caught in a Welcome Mat, any Attacker who is nearby can revive them by helping them get up on their feet but downed Attacker will only have 50hp once up.
	\n\nWelcome Mats are best placed in dark places where Attackers will not see them.
	\n\nFrost Mats are very useful when places next to Windows and Door as rushing Attacker will not notice it and get trapped.
	\n\nWelcome Mats combine best with Defenders who have Shield because, Shields can be placed in the doorway with Welcome Mat behind it. When Attackers vault the Shield, they will be trapped in the Mat.
	\n\nAttackers cannot move when downed in a Welcome Mat.\n\nWelcome Mats are best placed on top of stairs as Attackers will not see the trap as they move up the step and will be trapped.
	\n\nWhen Attackers are trapped in Frost Mat, they can be killed from below or above the floor by shooting at them. This require good map knowledge to execute.
	\n\nFrost Mats are very effective in trapping high speed operators when they are rushing the objective.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lesion_tip">Lesion uses his Gu Mines to cause damage to Attackers. It causes initial damage of 10 hp and 8 hp per 2 seconds until removed.
	\n\nWhen Attackers are removing Gu Mines, they dont have their Weapons in hand and are very vulnerable.
	\n\nGu Mines have radius of 1 m when deployed to be triggered by Attackers.
	\n\nGu Mines are best suited to prevent rush from Attackers especially Ash, Hibana, Iq and Capitao.
	\n\nWhen poisoned by Gu Mines, the Attacker cannot sprint.
	\n\nLesion is only Defender who can see the Gu Mines where they are placed. When Attacker comes in contact with the mines, the icon disappear thus providing valuable intel to Lesion. This can be effective in shooting Attackers through walls when Gu Mines are placed at certain locations.
	\n\nGu Mines are cloaked, but can be seen if one notice closely.
	\n\nLesion start with 1 Gu Mine at start of round and acquires one every 30 seconds.
	\n\nGu Mines are very effective in preventing Shield operators from pushing to the objective. If they come in contact with a Gu Mine, they will be very vulnerable when removing it.
	\n\nStepping on a Gu Mine cancels the boost provided by Finka to Attacker.
	\n\nWhen Attackers step on a Gu Mine, Defenders can hear a clank sound to denote that.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ela_tip">Ela Grizmot Mines can stick to any surface at any height.
	\n\nGrizmot Mines detonate when a Attacker is close by. It cancels their current action, disorients them, limit visual and disrupt their hearing.
	\n\nUnlike disoriented by Echo Yokai, moving around with Grizmot Mines triggered will not worsen the effect.
	\n\nEla is a powerful defender with her powerful Sub Machine Gun. It is almost impossible to win gunfights against Ela.
	\n\nDisoriented with Ela or Echo one after other will cancel the previous effect. Only one disorientation can be in place at a time.
	\n\nEla mines cannot cancel Attacker action of them pulling out needle from Lesion Gu Mines.
	\n\nEla when downed has another Concussion Mines which she can detonate to disorient nearby enemies to give other Defenders a chance to save her.
	\n\nEla recovers at a pace two times the speed of other Defenders when in contact with Zofia Concussion grenades They work in both ways.
	\n\nRook can increase the time of bleeding when Ela is down so she can detonate the last Concussion a bit later selectively targeted at Attacked who come nearby.
	\n\nGrizmot Mines detonate only if Attackers are in line of sight of the mine.
	\n\nGrizmot Mines blast radius is 6m while its proximity detonation radius is 4m.
	\n\nEla uses her Grizmot Mines to defend her close vicinity When someone triggers the mine, She pushed hard and gets the kill.
	\n\nGrizmot Mines can also be used to collect intel about Attackers if they have entered any particular room in which the mine was placed.\n\n</string>

    <string name="vigil_tip">Vigil uses his ERC7 video disruptor to erase  himself from showing up in cameras and drones.
	\n\nERC7 takes a second to make Vigil fully visible to the cameras and drones.
	\n\nVigil ERC7 will deplete in 12 seconds.
	\n\nVigil ERC7 will take 6 seconds to recharge.
	\n\nERC7 has a time duration in which it can be active, It need to be recharged to be used again.
	\n\nWhen Vigil fires a gun or affects the environment, The ERC7 will stop the mechanism and make him visible.\n\nWhen Vigil is in a area under cloak, the camera feed will have a unique interference border to denote his presence in the room.
	\n\nVigil EERC will turn the red light of drones into white when jamming them.
    \n\nVideo Disruptor ERC7 has a range of 12m.
	\n\nVigil can be very effective in roaming and can waste a lot of time for Attackers.
	\n\nVigil cannot be droned out by Attackers, His exact location can never be found by Attackers.\n\n</string>


    <!-- OPERATOR COMBINE -->

    <string name="sledge_combine">Sledge can create new line of sight for Glaz and Glaz can provide support for him from long range.
	\n\nSledge works well with Thermite, Buck and Hibana. They all combined can create havoc by destroying everything (walls, barricades, floors and hatches). They are the defenders nightmare.
	\n\nSledge works well with Jackal to track any enemies below the floor and create holes in floors to kill them from above.
	\n\nSledge can help Thatcher to help him throw EMPs at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.
	\n\nSledge can help Ying to help her throw Candelas at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.
	\n\nSledge can help Capitao to help him fire arrows at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.\n\n</string>

    <string name="thatcher_combine">Thatcher works well with Hibana and Thermite to help open walls if they are jammed with Mute Signal Disruptors or Bandit Shock Wires.
	\n\nThatcher works well with Iq to detect defender gadgets and eliminate them.
	\n\nTwitch can help Thatcher save his EMPs by destroying gadgets with her drone.
	\n\nThatcher can combine with Stun grenade operators to prevent EMP being destroyed by Jager Active Defense Systems by using Stun grenades to waste the Active Defense Systems.
	\n\nThatcher can use the EMP to help an aggressive Attacker like Ash, by clearing out the way and removing any Defender gadgets like Gu Mines, Ela Grizmot mines and more.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ash_combine">Ash works well with other three speed operators Hibana, Capitao, Iq in a very aggressive manner to rush the objective and kill all Defenders.
	\n\nAsh works well with Buck ,Sledge and Hibana to break the surrounding walls and floors.\n\n</string>

    <string name="thermite_combine">Thermite works well with Hibana and they combined can destroy most of the walls and hatches.
	\n\nThatcher can help Thermite if the area to be destroyed is jammed by Mute Signal Disruptors or Bandit Shock Wired. Thatcher can remove them with his EMP.
	\n\nTwitch can help remove the Mute Signal Disruptor or Bandit Shock Wires.
	\n\nZofia can help Thermite in certain places and help disorient Bandit via drone hole and prevent him from doing the Bandit trick.
	\n\nIq can help Thermite to see if Bandit is tricking the other side of wall.
	\n\nThermite can open walls for Glaz to cover from long distance.
	\n\nSledge, Buck, Iq can help Thermite in certain places to kill Bandit via drone hole with Grenades if he is in close proximity to the drone hole and is active Bandit tricking.\n\n</string>

    <string name="twitch_combine">Twitch Drones can be used to distract Defenders while other Attackers are pushing aggressive.
	\n\nTwitch works best with Thatcher and Iq at taking out Defender gadgets as a whole.
	\n\nTwitch can help Thermite in removing Mute Jammers or Bandit Shock Wires on the other side of the wall.
	\n\nTwitch is very useful in removing Jager ADS which blocks projectiles into the room.\n\n</string>

    <string name="montagne_combine">Montagne works with Ash,Thermite and Hibana who can create entry for him.
	\n\nMontagne, Blitz, Glaz and Ying can be combined to perform a methodical Smoke plant, where all use their smokes and Ying uses her candelas to perform the plant in the confusion. Blitz can cover the Defuser at short range while Glaz covers it at long range.
	\n\nMontagne can use his smoke grenades to help him with his thermal scope.\n\n</string>

    <string name="glaz_combine">Thermite, Hibana, Sledge and Buck can create new lines of sight to help Glaz get new line of sight.
	\n\nGlaz, Ying , Blitz and Montagne can be combined to perform a methodical Smoke plant It is very hard to deny Blitz can cover the Defuser at short range while Glaz covers it at long range.\n\n</string>

    <string name="fuze_combine">Fuze works well with Jackal to track any enemies below and fuzing them from above.
	\n\nFuze works well with Montagne to lock Defenders into a room and fuzing them from above.
	\n\nFuze can help cover defuser after plant by pre placing cluster charges above defuser and activating them when Defenders try to defuse.\n\n</string>

    <string name="blitz_combine">Blitz can be used to smoke plant the defuser and cover it in short range When combined with Glaz, Montagne and Ying, They can easily plant Defuser.
	\n\nBlitz can use his smoke grenades to help Glaz with his thermal scope.\n\n</string>

    <string name="iq_combine">Iq with Thermite can help kill Bandit through drone holes if Bandit is tricking in the vicinity of the drone hole.
	\n\nIq can help Thatcher and Thermite in detecting if Bandit is tricking for Thermite.
	\n\nIq can help Thatcher identify areas where gadgets are placed to throw EMP at.
	\n\nIq works well with Dokkaebi, When she calls, Iq can detect the phones if Defenders are trying to switch them off.\n\n</string>

    <string name="buck_combine">Buck can combine with Thermite, Hibana and Sledge They combined can destroy almost all surfaces and create chaos.
	\n\nBuck can create new lines of sight for Glaz to cover from a distance.
	\n\nBuck can also be used to destroy Mira Black Mirror by shooting from below the floor or above the floor. It requires good map knowledge.
	\n\nBuck can help Thatcher to help him throw EMPs at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.
	\n\nBuck can help Ying to help her throw Candelas at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.
	\n\nBuck can help Capitao to help him fire arrows at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.\n\n</string>

    <string name="blackbeard_combine">Blackbeard works well with Shield operators like Fuze, Blitz and Montagne That is a lot of shields to deal with.
	\n\nBlackbeard is very useful to hold flank angle It is very difficult to kill a blackbeard when his body is not visible.\n\n</string>

    <string name="capitao_combine">Capitao Smoke mode can be used to help plant Defuser and is best combined with Blitz, Glaz, Ying and Montagne With all their smokes Defenders can be made unaware of the Defuser plant location.
	\n\nCapitao can use his smoke grenades to help Glaz with his thermal scope.
	\n\nCapitao can be combined with Buck and Sledge Buck or Sledge can create new line of sight in floor and Capitao can use it to fire his bolts.
	\n\nCapitao can be used aggressively to rush the objective with Ash, Hibana, Twitch and Sledge .\n\n</string>

    <string name="hibana_combine">Thermite along with Hibana can open holes in walls when under Bandit trick Use X-KAIROS on both walls and place Exothermic charge on one side Denote them both at same time, this way Bandit cannot prevent any one side from opening.
	\n\nHibana with Capitao, Ash and Iq can be used aggressively and rush into objective.\n\n</string>

    <string name="jackal_combine">Jackal when combined with Dokkaebi is very useful in finding the Roamers.
	\n\nFuze and Jackal can locate the roamer and drive them out of the room using his Cluster charges.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ying_combine">Ying works best with Glaz, Blitz and Montagne to do a Defuser Plant that is hard to deny.
	\n\nYing works with Fuze, When Ying blinds Defenders, Fuze can detonate the Cluster Charges to wreak havoc.
	\n\nSledge and Buck can help Ying to help her throw Candelas at critical location by creating new lines of sight in floors or walls.
	\n\nThatcher can help Ying in removing Jager ADS before she throws the Candela.\n\n</string>

    <string name="zofia_combine">Zofia works well with Buck, Sledge, Hibana and Thermite They all combined can destroy most of the walls and floors.
	\n\nZofia can be used to disorient Bandit if Bandit tricking This is possible if there is a drone hole next to where Bandit is tricking.\n\n</string>

    <string name="dokkaebi_combine">Dokkaebi works with Iq to detect phones when Defenders are trying to switch them off.
	\n\nDokkaebi works with Attackers like Ash, Hibana, Capitao and Iq While Dokkaebi calls Defenders, they can rush the objective and kill theDefenders who are trying to switch off their phones.
	\n\nDokkaebi and Jackal combined can be very effective in finding the roamer and killing them.\n\n</string>

    <string name="finka_combine">Finka abililty is very powerful when combined with Attackers having Light Machine Guns and Machine Pistols as their recoils are reduced to large extent.
	\n\nFinka can help Attackers recover from Ela Mines by using her ability.
	\n\nFinka can be used well with Attackers having Stun Grenades Finka boost will recover Attackers from the flash faster.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lion_combine">Lion ability works well when the Defuser has been planted Using his ability will detect Defenders approaching the Defuser.
	\n\nLion works well with Jackal to track the position of Roamers and resist their movement.
	\n\nFuze can be combined with Lion to lock defenders in a room and fuzing to kill them or injure them a lot.
    \n\nLion works well with Thermite to detect the Bandit Trick.\n\n</string>

    <string name="smoke_combine">Smoke can be combined with Defenders having Barbed wire Using smoke gas grenades when Attackers are moving through barbed wire will deal them with more damage.
	\n\nSmoke works well with Mira Staying behind the cover of Mira Black Mirrors, Smoke can prevent Attackers from planting defuser by using hisSmoke gas grenades over the plant spot.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mute_combine">Mute works well with Mira When placed behind wall where Mira Black mirror is present, it will prevent Attacker from opening the wall This is very effective in preventing Hibana from opening Mira walls.
	\n\nMute works well with Bandit, Mute can be used to waste Thatcher EMP so that Bandit can later Shock wire the wall and Attacker have no way to open the shocked wall.
	\n\nMute works well with Castle Armor panels If placed in range of the armor panel, Attackers will not be able to breach the panel because their detonation device will be jammed.\n\n</string>

    <string name="castle_combine">Pulse can be used with Castle to detect enemy movements beyond the Armor Panel and take necessary action.
	\n\nMira strategies can be used with Castle to protect Mira while she uses her Black Mirror to the advantage of the Defenders.\n\n</string>

    <string name="pulse_combine">Pulse can be combines with other nitro cell operators to pre-place them and detonate by communicating with team mates.
	\n\nPulse along with Caveira, Ela, Jager and Vigil can be used for aggressive roaming.
	\n\nPulse can be used with Bandit to detect where Thermite is placing his Exothermic charge and help in Bandit trick.\n\n</string>

    <string name="doc_combine">Doc works better with Rook to greatly improve the armor characteristics of Defenders.
	\n\nDoc works best with Rook because wearing a rook armor will down the Defender before being killed by Attacker, Doc when timed correctly can save the downed Defender.\n\n</string>

    <string name="rook_combine">Rook works best with Doc who can revive Defenders when they are down.\n\n</string>

    <string name="kapkan_combine">Kapkan works well with Roamers and help them know if a Attacker is nearby Detonation of a EDD device will alert Defenders about a nearby Attacker.\n\n</string>

    <string name="tachanka_combine">Tachanka can combine with Doc and Rook to hold the objective from the Attackers They combined can deal high amount of gunfire.
	\n\nTachanka works well with Jager, where his ADS will prevent anyone from destroying the shield from distance ADS will block the incoming grenades targeted at destroying the shield.\n\n</string>

    <string name="jager_combine">Jager works well with Anchor Defenders and prevent Attackers from using explosive grenades at them.
	\n\nJager works well with other roamers Ela, Pulse and Caveira to prevent Attackers from approaching the objective.\n\n</string>

    <string name="bandit_combine">Bandit can be a effective roamer given his high agility He works well with other roamers like Pulse, Ela, Jager and Caveira.
	\n\nBandit Shock wires can be used with Castle Armor Panels with Barbed wire underneath to deal damage to Attackers who come for breaching the Panels.
	\n\nBandit can combine with Mira and can help the wall where Black Mirror is placed from being destroyed by Hibana or Thermite.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mira_combine">Mira walls can be best covered from hot breachers like Thermite and Hibana by using Bandit Shock Wire on the wall.
	\n\nMira works well with Mute who can help in preventing the Mira wall being open by Hibana or Thermite Mute Jammers will prevent Hibana or Thermite from activating the charge.\n\n</string>

    <string name="valkyrie_combine">Valkyrie works well with Defenders having Nitro cellsBlack Eyes are very useful for tracking Attackers above the floor and killing them with the help of Nitro cell to the floor. This requires good map knowledge to implement.
	\n\nBlack Eyes Cameras can be great source for information for Roamers especially Caveira.
	\n\nWhen Black Eye cameras are hacked by Dokkaebi, Vigil cannot be seen in it</string>

    <string name="caveira_combine">Caveira works best with Valyrie who can help her providing intel about Attackers with help of her Black Eye Cameras.
	\n\nCaveira works best with Pulse who can provide her with the intel of Attacker movement.
	\n\nCaveira works well with Lesion, Gu Mines if down any Attacker Caveira can interrogate them.\n\n</string>

    <string name="echo_combine">Yokai drone when combined with Ela can produce a series of disorientation to Attackers in group This will render them vulnerable.
	\n\nEla and Yokai drone effect on same Attacker will only produce latest effect on the Attacker cancelling the previous one.
	\n\nEcho can be very helpful in collecting intel and  assisting Roamers in Attackers movements.\n\n</string>

    <string name="frost_combine">Frost works well with Defenders who have deployable shield Placing frost mat next to shiled will down the Attacker who tries to vault the shield.
	\n\nSmoke can help in killing Attackers who are trapped in Frost Map by using his smoke gas grenade from longer distance.
	\n\nFrost works well with Lesion Gu Mines, When placed in close proximity to a Frost Mat,Attackers can be killed instantly.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lesion_combine">Lesion works well with Frost, When Gu Mines are placed close to Welcome Mat, it can kill and Attacker instantly. Be careful not to place the Gu Mines very close to Welcome Mat which will disable the effect of Gu Mines
	n\nGu Mines work well with Kapktan EDD When placed in near proximity to it, it will cause a total damage of 70hp and more.
	\n\nGu Mines work with Ela traps, This allows the Attacker to be disoriented and poisoned at the same time.
	\n\nGu Mines can down Attackers if they are not careful which provides opportunity for Caveira to interrogate them.
	\n\nLesion Gu Mines can be used to detect Attacker Movement above and with little coordination with Nitro cell operators, It can used to blow up Attackers from below.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ela_combine">Echo when working with Ela can cause a set of disorientation to group of Attackers who are pushing in same area.
	\n\nDisoriented with Ela or Echo one after other will cancel the previous effect Only one disorientation can be in place at a time.\n\n</string>

    <string name="vigil_combine">Vigil works well with roamers like Pulse, Jager and Caveira.
	\n\nVigil shotgun can create small hole in Castle Armor Panel, This can be used to kill unwary Attackers.\n\n</string>


    <!-- OPERATOR COUNTER -->

    <string name="sledge_counter">Pulse can be used to detect the movement of Sledge as he moves around breaking stuff.
	\n\nDefenders can reinforce walls and hatches to prevent Sledge from breaking it.
	\n\nRoamers are very effective in flanking Sledge from behind while he is busy breaking stuff.
	\n\nValkyrie can spy on Sledge with the help of her Black Eye Cameras.
	\n\nEcho drone can be used to disorient Sledge and prevent him from breaking floors and walls.\n\n</string>

    <string name="thatcher_counter">Jager Active Defense Systems can destroy EMPs when caught in its line of sight while throwing.
	\n\nEcho drone most times will be very high in ceiling and will not be affected by EMP as their range is short.
	\n\nEMP do not affect mechanical devices like Mira Black Mirror or Frost Welcome Mat.
	\n\nWhen Thatcher throws an EMP, Defenders can easily track his position because the light from EMP will make the angle thrown from easily detectable.
	\n\nWhen combining with Thermite, throw an EMP only when Thermite is in active position to place the Exothermic Charge to bypass Bandit trick.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ash_counter">CREM breaches can be electrified and are destroyed if they come in contact with Bandit Shock Wire  Shield or Barbed Wire.
	\n\nJager Active Defense System will destroy the CREM breaches if in line of sight.
	\n\nAsh rush into the objective can be prevented with the help of Gu Mines, Ela Proximity mines,Frost Welcome Mats,Castle Armor Panels and Kapkan EDDs.\n\n</string>

    <string name="thermite_counter">Thermite Exothermic Charges can be jammed by Mute Signal Disruptor from Detonation.
	\n\nExothermic Charges can be destroyed by Bandit Shock Wires This counter by Bandit is called the "Bandit Trick" while he actively places aShock Wire to the wall while Thermite sets an Exothermic Charge thereby destroying it.
	\n\nExothermic Charges release visible sparks on other side of wall to denote its activation and detonation.
	\n\nPulse can be used to detect the position of placement of Thermite Exothermic charges and help in Bandit trick.
	\n\nValkyrie can be used to spy Thermite with her Black Eye cameras and help in Bandit trick.
	\n\nMira can be used on the wall to see where Thermite is placing his Exothermic charges and help in Bandit trick.\n\n</string>

    <string name="twitch_counter">Defender Shields blocking entrances eliminate the movement of Twitch Drone into the room. This is a reliable method to protect Mira Black Mirrors.
	\n\nTwitch Drones get destroyed if it comes in contact with Bandit Shoch Wires.
	\n\nTwitch Drones are jammed when in contact with Mute Signal Disruptors.\n\n</string>

    <string name="montagne_counter">Montagne is vulnerable from behind very much Be on the lookout for roamers.
	\n\nMontagne is comparatively slower than heavy operators.
	\n\nMontagne is only covered 80 degrees and not 90 degrees at both sides and is vulnerable a little bit at the sides.
	\n\nEla Grizmot mines can lower his fully extended shield when in contact.
	\n\nEcho Yokai can disorient him and lower his fully extended shield when in contact.\n\nMontagne is louder when moving like other shield operators.
	\n\nFrost Mats will injure Montagne even when his shield is fully extended.
	\n\nBandit shock wires will damage him when he touches it.
	\n\nSmoke Gas grenades are ideal to prevent Montagne from entering sites and push him back.
	\n\nA nitro cell thrown behind Montagne when detonated will down or kill him.
	\n\nLesion Gu Mines are ideal to prevent Montagne from pushing forward into the objective Once in contact with a Gu Mine, He is very vulnerable when removing it.\n\n</string>

    <string name="glaz_counter">Glaz is very vulnerable in short range as his weapon is hard to use in short range.
	\n\nCastle Armor Panels can used to close entrances to objectives and prevent Glaz from peeking from long distance.
	\n\nReinforcing critical walls will prevent Glaz from breaking it and peeking inside.
	\n\nJager ADS can destroy Smoke grenades from Glaz and prevent him from using his Thermal Scope.\n\n</string>

    <string name="fuze_counter">Mute Signal Disruptor can jam the Cluster charge from being activated.
	\n\nThere is a distinct sound made when placing the Cluster Chargess This audio cue can be used by Defenders to vacate the room or shoot the charge. Jager Active Defense systems can destroy pellets as they come in line of sight to them.
	\n\nReinforcing walls and hatches will prevent Fuze from placing his Cluster Charges.
	\n\nFuze when placing his Cluster Charges are very vulnerable and cannot defend himself Roamers can locate Fuze easily based on the detonation sound.
	\n\nPulse is very effective in detecting Fuze with his Heartbeat Scanner Pulse can closely follow Fuze and kill him in cover.\n\n</string>

    <string name="blitz_counter">Blitz shield moves away left when melee attacked to the front leaving Blitz open and vulnerable in the front, He must quickly turn right to bring the shield in front of him to prevent any frontal damage.
	\n\nMute Signal Disruptor will jam Blitz Flash Shield if in its radius.
	\n\nGu Mines are very effective in preventing Blitz from pushing aggressively into objective.
	\n\nEla Grizmot mines help prevent Blitz from pushing aggressively.\n\nEcho Yokai Drone can be used to disorient and distract Blitz.
	\n\nKapkan traps prevent Blitz from entering objective.\n\nFrost Mats will down Blitz when he is in contact with it.
	\n\nCastle Armor panels can be used to deny entry access to Blitz into the objective.
	\n\nNitro cells on doorways and windows can be used to prevent Blitz from entering them As Blitz cannot shoot it, If he enters he can be killed easily.\n\n</string>

    <string name="iq_counter">Iq can only use her pistol when she scans for Defender gadgets The pistol is very limited in terms of firing power so she is very vulnerable in that time period.\n\n</string>

    <string name="buck_counter">Buck is vulnerable to Roamers while breaking stuff if not careful,especially Caveira.
	\n\nDefenders can reinforce walls and floors to prevent Buck from opening them.\n\nPulse can be used to detect the movement of Buck as he moves around breaking stuff.\n\n</string>

    <string name="blackbeard_counter">Vigil shotgun will break the shield on any level when dealt with.
	\n\nEla submachine gun is very aggressive to deal Blackbeard .\n\nSmoke SMG and Mira Vector are effective weapons to deal Blackbeard Be on the lookout for them.
	\n\nBlackbeard can be killed easily if shot in legs and body.
	\n\nNever peek a Blackbeard unless you are confident you can kill himYou are at a great disadvantage by peeking him.
	\n\nCastle Armor Panels are very useful in preventing Blackbeard from peeking the windows.\n\n</string>

    <string name="capitao_counter">Nitro cell is very effective to use in smoke and deny Defuser plant if Capitao is trying to smoke and plant.
	\n\nLesion Gu Mines are effective in preventing Capitao from rushing into the objective.
	\n\nEla Grizmot mines are effective in preventing Capitao from rushing into the objective.
	\n\nKapkan traps are effective in denying Capitao the entrance into objective.\n\nFrost Mats are effective in trapping Capitao who rushes into objective.
	\n\nIf you are cornered with a Asphyxiating Bolt, try to find alternative location and relocate quickly.\n\n</string>

    <string name="hibana_counter">Mute Signal Disruptors prevent you from detonating X-KAIROS pellets.
	\n\nX-KAIROS pellets will be destoyed if is in contct with Bandit Shock wire.
	\n\nX-KAIROS pellets can be destroyed by gunfire or explosives Defenders can use nitro cell or impact grenade to destroy the pellet in activation and prevent it from opening walls or floors.\n\n</string>

    <string name="jackal_counter">Thatcher or Twitch can help Jackal by removing the Mute Signal Disruptors.
	\n\nJackal works well with Sledge, Buck to track any enemies below the floor and create holes in floors to kill them from above.
	\n\nCaveira is a direct counter to Jackal, Eventhough she can be tracked by him, When she enters Silent Step, Her location will not be ping like other Defenders.
	\n\nCaveira, When she times the ping made by Eyenox by moving into Silent Step cannot be detected by Jackal in any manner.
	\n\nEyenox cannot be turned ON or OFF while holding a hostage.
	\n\nMute Signal Disruptors will interfere with his Eyenox causing static effect, which almost makes him blind.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ying_counter">Jager Active Defense Systems are capable of destoying it when thrown as a whole.
	\n\nBarbed wires will reduce Candela rolling speed.
	\n\nBandit Shock Wires is capable of destroying Candelas when in contact with.
	\n\nDefenders looking into the site with the help of Cameras will not be blinded if Candela is in the feed of the camera.\n\n</string>

    <string name="zofia_counter">Ela is resistant to Zofia Concussion effects, allowing her to recover twice as fast as other Defenders.
	\n\nJager Active Defense System can take out Zofia grenades if they are not detonated when coming into line of sight of the ADS.
	\n\nDefenders can reinforce walls and floors to prevent Zofia from opening them.\n\n</string>

    <string name="dokkaebi_counter">When Logic Bomb calls are activated, Defenders can try to hide and switch it off to prevent it from ringing.
	\n\nDoekkabi takes time to do calls or camera hacks, during this time she is very vulnerable and cannot move.
	\n\nThe Defender phones are destroyable, which must be destroyed by another Defender if one  dies to prevent Dokkaebi from hacking into the Defender Camera Network.
	\n\nWhen Defender cameras are hacked it displays a logo to show it is hacked for the Defenders, Defenders should shoot the hacked cameras to prevent giving away their location.
	\n\nDokkaebi cannot call Echo and cannot hack into Echo Drone.\n\nWhen Defenders are in range of Mute Signal Disruptors, their phones will not ring when called.
	\n\nBandit Shock Wires will destroy Defender phones when in contact.\n\nVigil cannot be seen in hacked camera feed.\n\n</string>

    <string name="finka_counter">When under Finka boost Attackers will take more damage from Smoke toxic gas grenades.
	\n\nWhen under Finka boost Attackers will be detectable at a longer distance in Pulse Cardiac Sensor.
	\n\nFinka boost will be cancelled when hit by Echo Yokai drone or Lesion Gu mines.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lion_counter">Defenders are given a warning of 3 seconds before the scan takes place to position themselves in a safe place.
	\n\nDefenders can do all actions except position movement and not be detected by the EE-One-D drone.
	\n\nDefenders can move about freely and do all actions when they are in close proximity to a Mute Jammer.\n\n</string>

    <string name="smoke_counter">Thatcher can destroy the gas grenades using his EMP.
	\n\nIq can detect smoke gas grenades and shoot them.\n\nTwitch can destroy smoke gas grenades with her drones.
	\n\nHigh speed Attackers are more likely to escape through the smoke taking less damage than Low speed Attackers.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mute_counter">Thatcher can destroy Mute Disruptors when in Range.
	\n\nIq can detect Mute Disruptors and shoot them through floors, windows and doors.
	\n\nTwitch can destroy them using her drone But if the drone is too close, it will be disrupted too.
	\n\nWhen drones are jammed by Mute Disruptors, Attackers can destroy the jammer and recover their drones.
	\n\nMechanical devices are not affected by Signal Disruptors.\n\n</string>

    <string name="castle_counter">Effective ways to destroy them are using Breach charges and Grenades.
	\n\nAsh, Zofia and Hibana can destroy the Armor Panels from a safe distance.
	\n\nSledge Breaching Hammer and Thermite charge can take down Armor Panels easily.
	\n\nGlaz can 12 shot Armor Panel with his sniper to destroy them.
	\n\nFuze Cluster Charges, Ying Candela and Doekkabi shotgun create holes in Armor Panels for new line of sight.
	\n\nArmor Panel can be destroyed by melee attack 12 times.\n\n</string>

    <string name="pulse_counter">Thatchers EMP grenade will disable Heartbeat Sensor for a while before it can be reused.
	\n\nThe sound Heartbeat Sensor emits will get louder as Attackers get close to it.
	\n\nDokkaebi can call Defenders, therrby giving away the position of Pulse.
	\n\nJackal is very effective in tracking Pulse foottracks and detecting his current position.
	\n\nIq can detect Pulse when he is using the Heartbeat Sensor Iq can effectively try to locate him shoot through surfaces.\n\n</string>

    <string name="doc_counter">Doc can be prevented from reviving any Defender by quickly killing them after they are downed.\n\n</string>

    <string name="rook_counter">Rook Satchel can be destroyed by team mates or Attackers.
	\n\nAttackers can also wear Rook Armor Plates if found.
	\n\nTwitch Shock drone can be used to kill Defenders who are downed.
	\n\nCapitao can use his asphyxiating bolts to kill downed Defenders too.
	\n\nAny Attacker who can do any Damage with gadget can kill downed Defenders Even throwing a flashbang can kill a downed Defender.\n\n</string>

    <string name="kapkan_counter">Kapkan traps can be destroyed by Thatcher EMP.
	\n\nTwitch can destroy the Kapkan traps.\n\nAny Attacker gadget when detonates, if the Kapkan trap is in the radius of the explosion will be destroyed.
	\n\nKapkan traps can be destoyed by normal gunfire.
	\n\nDrones can be effectively used to follow Kapkan and find where he places his traps.
	\n\nIq can detect the Kapkan traps and destroy it.\n\n</string>

    <string name="tachanka_counter">Montagne can deal bullets from LMG.
	\n\nAsh and Zofia are capable of shooting LMG with their grenades to destroy the front shield making the Defender who uses it vulnerable.
	\n\nCapitao asphyxiating bolts are very effective to kill Defender who is using the mounted LMG.\n\n</string>

    <string name="jager_counter">Stun Grenade and Ying Candela can be used to burn out the ADS to further use Frag grenades to throw at Defenders. Thatcher can destroy the ADS if in radius of the EMP.
	\n\nTwitch can destoy the ADS by using her drone .
	\n\nJager ADS can be destroyed by normal gunfire.
	\n\nIq can detect the Jager ADS and destroy it.\n\n</string>

    <string name="bandit_counter">Bandit Shock wires can be destroyed  by normal gunfire.
	\n\nThatcher EMP will destroy the Shock wire if in radius.
	\n\nTwitch can use her drone to destroy Bandit Shock wire.
	\n\nBandit when tricking for Thermite is very vulnerable from behind.
	\n\nIq can detect the Bandit shock wire and destroy it.
	\n\nBandit Shock wire can be destroyed by Attacker explosion gadgets if it comes in contact with them.\n\n</string>

    <string name="mira_counter">Any explosion device when in contact with the Gas canister in Black Mirrors will open it.
	\n\nTwitch drones can destroy Black Mirrors leaving a hole in middle of the wall Nothing can be done to remove the hole in wall.
	\n\nBuck, Sledge or Ash can be used to open Mira Black Mirrors from below and above the floor, Be careful in their placements.
	\n\nNon-reinforced walls cannot be reinforced if a Black Mirror was placed in wall.
	\n\nMira can place Black Mirror at elevated height if she can reach so.
	\n\nMira Black Mirror can be opened by Defenders by melee, bullet , nitro, impacting the gas canister in it.
	\n\nYing will flash people in Mira Black Mirror  even when it is not open.
	\n\nIf Black Mirror is placed on unreinforced wall, destruction on the wall will destroy the Black Mirror too.
	\n\nThermite and Hibana can destroy Mira Black Mirrors Be on the lookout for them.
	\n\nDouble Mira Black Mirrors with one open and one closed is a common strategy to intimidate Attackers with prefire.\n\n</string>

    <string name="valkyrie_counter">Thatcher EMP grenades will destroy Black Eyes.
	\n\nTwitch can destroy Black Eyes with her darts.\n\nIq is a direct counter to Valkyrie, She can detect any cameras thrown outside and prevent the advantage it has for Defenders.
	\n\nDokkaebi can hack into Defender camera network including Black Eyes when she hacks a dead Defender phone.
	\n\nAny explosion device when in contact with the Black Eye camera will destroy it.\n\n</string>

    <string name="caveira_counter">Interrogation will take 3 seconds and Caveira is vulnerable in that time.
	\n\nDokkaebi can call and locate Caveira Have a rotation route planned if you are pinned down by Attackers.
	\n\nAlways drone to find out the position of Caveira She can be very lethal.
	\n\nCaveira is the ultimate roamer, cover you flanks and always be ready to confront her.\n\n</string>

    <string name="echo_counter">Yokai drone when combined with Ela can produce a series of disorientation to Attackers in group This will render them vulnerable.
	\n\nEla and Yokai drone effect on same Attacker will only produce latest effect on the Attacker canceling the previous one.
	\n\nEcho can be very helpful in collecting intel and  assisting Roamers in Attackers movements.\n\n</string>

    <string name="frost_counter">Frost Welcome Mats can destroyed by a melee hit but must be done carefully or it may down you Hit the part that does not activate the trap.
	\n\nFrost traps will get destroyed if in radius of a explosion from Attacker gadget.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lesion_counter">Gu Mines can be destroyed by Thatcher EMP when in range.
	\n\nGu mines can be destroyed by Gunfire and any explosion near to it, like Frag grenades, Ash CREM and more.
	\n\nIq can detect Gu Mines though her Scanner and destroy them.\n\n</string>

    <string name="ela_counter">Iq can detect Ela Grizmot Mines and destroy them through surfaces.
	\n\nTwitch can destroy Grizmot Mines and she makes this as her main priority.
	\n\nThatcher can destroy any Grizmot Mines in radious of his EMP.
	\n\nAny number of Attackers caught in the Grizmot Mines detonation proximity will be disoriented.
	\n\nGrizmot Mines are destroyed by destruction nearby like Frag grenades, Ash CREM and more.
	\n\nZofia is less affected by Ela Grizmot minesThe Grizmot mine effect only last for half the time it lasts for other Defenders.
	\n\nMontagne can be used to clear out the Ela mines from under the cover of his Extended Shield.\n\n</string>

    <string name="vigil_counter">Jackal is very effective in tracking Vigil and counter him.
	\n\nDokkaebi can call Vigil and find his location based on the sound from his phone ring.
	\n\nEven when Vigil in cloak, he can be heard in drones and cameras if hacked by Dokkaebi.
	\n\nIq can detect Vigil when the ERC7 is active.
	\n\nThatcher can temporarily disable the ERC7 of Vigil.
	\n\nTwitch can temporarily disable the ERC7 when she shoots the dart into Vigil.
	\n\nFuze is effective in pushing Vigil out of a room by using his Cluster charges in that room.\n\n</string>


</resources>
